梦工厂出品
英灵殿  这里是  雷神
Valhalla, this is Thor.
我们可能找到一名重要目标
We have visual on a possible high-value target.
雷神  这里是  英灵殿
Thor, this is Valhalla.
我们正在确认被护送的目标身份
We're seeking positive ID on target traveling in convoy
我们会为你们提供更多的支援
and we're pushing more assets your way.
在副频道上联系  洛基
Contact Loki on secondary net.
洛基  这里是  雷神
Loki, this is Thor.
目标在坐标  2-4-T-K-B
Target is located at grid coordinates two-four-Tango-Kilo-Bravo
1-2-4-5-6-7-3-9
one-two-four-five-six-seven-three-niner.
确认你的视讯
Confirm you have visual.
目标确认中
Verifying target ID.
连线电眼和红外线传感器
Electro-optic and infrared sensors are online.
- 目标确认中  - 国防部长马上到
- Confirming target. - SecDef is arriving now.
部长先生  这边请
Mr. Secretary, this way, sir.
尝试连接目标的手机
Attempting cell phone link to moving target.
准备接受数据
Stand by for data feed.
准备接受音频
Stand by for audio.
收到
Got it.
别告诉我你只在沙尘暴中看到他的胡子
Now, don't tell me you spotted the beard in the middle of a goddamn sandstorm.
- 确定是他吗 - 长官  我们正在确认中
- Is it really him? - We're confirming that now, sir.
长官  马上收到音频
Sir, audio is coming up now.
- 确认声音指纹  - 中士  能查到什么
- Verifying voice pattern match. - What do we have here, Sergeant?
四名男性  其中一名操着 拉赫沙尼方言
Four males. One of them is speaking in Rakhshani dialect,
这和  胡艾  的资料是符合的
consistent with our intel on al-Khoei.
长官  我们刚刚收到这个
Sir, it's just coming up.
37%  符合跟  "可能"  完全不相干
"Thirty-seven percent" and "probable" don't belong in the same sentence.
我不可能给总统这种答复
I'm not taking this to the President.
基于英国方面提供的可信资料  中情局
CIA and NCTC concur it is the target,
还有  NCTC/国家反恐中心  一致认定目标
based on reliable intel from the Brits.
他们要离开公路了
They're pulling off the highway.
条件不够充足  建议放弃任务
Criteria is not met. Recommend abort.
电脑  建议放弃任务
We have an abort recommendation.
这家伙两年难得现身一次  机不可失
If it's him, this guy comes out of hiding every couple of years at best.
长官  目标出现在东北角落
Sir, target is appearing around the northeast corner.
持有  AK-47  RPG/肩式火箭  丛林导弹
We've got AK-47s, RPGs and Chaparral guided missiles.
部长  这是个训练营
This is a training camp, Mr. Secretary.
再等等  51%  符合
Wait. Wait. Print. 51%. OFFICER 1: 51%.
电脑依然  建议放弃任务
Abort rec still holds.
我们没法得到更多资讯了
All other PID options exhausted.
长官  您的决定是?
ADMIRAL: What do you suggest we do, sir?
那是武器库吗?
Is that a weapons cache?
长官  从那洞穴周围的石头摆置
Sir, the placement of the stones around the pit,
以及五根伊斯兰教支柱来看  这是个葬礼
marker for the five pillars of Islam. I think it's a funeral.
我的老天
For Christ's sake.
顾问官  这会触犯哪些日内瓦公约?
Counsel, how many ways would this violate the Geneva Convention?
会触犯伤害非战斗人员条款
We can invoke hors de combat.
但我们也没足够资料确认这是个葬礼
There's no independent intel verifying that this is, in fact, a funeral.
长官  总统阁下从空军一号来电
Signal's got the President from Air Force One, sir.
总统阁下
Mr. President,
我们资料显示  51%  符合  马德 胡艾 特征
we have a 51% identity match on Majid al-Khoei.
坏消息是  他可能正在参加一个葬礼
The bad news is, there's some possibility he's at a funeral.
而且电脑建议  放弃任务
You should also be aware we have an abort recommendation.
但是参谋长议会建议执行任务
But the Joint Chiefs are urging a go.
好吧  那么你的建议是什么?
All right, what's your recommendation?
阁下  我们的目的是把所有伤亡减少到最小
Sir, we measure success by the least amount of collateral damage.
但是只有  51%  符合  这个风险太高了
At 51% probability, the risk is too high.
如果这是  胡艾  而且我们让他逃跑
And if it is al-Khoei and he walks,
我们的人民就会有危险
I'm putting our people at risk.
执行任务
You have a go.
谢谢您  总统阁下
Thank you, Mr. President.
-准备攻击  -准备攻击
- We're weapons hot! -  We have weapons hot!
洛基  你可以攻击
Loki, you are cleared to engage.
重复一遍  准备攻击
Repeat, weapons hot. PID.
我们连接上  "MQ9死神"  无人机
We have handshake with the MQ9 Reaper.
传送图像中
Sending you images now.
-洛基  收到坐标  -是的长官  切换红外线传感器
- Loki, target coordinates received. - Yes, sir. Switching to IR sensor.
激光锁定目标
Target is lased.
主武器上膛
Master arm on.
导弹发射
Missiles away.
10秒后命中
Ten seconds to impact.
《鹰眼》
伙计们  你们要赶快决定
You got to make a choice, fellas.
你们还算男人吗?
Who are you going to be? Boys or men?
- 我退出  - 怎么啦?
- I'm out on this one. - Why?
- 因为我破产了  - 别这样
- 'Cause I'm broke. - Come...
我怎么知道你底牌是不是比我大
How do I know you don't have something great under there?
科安  刚刚退出了
Kwame just paired the board.
看看桌上的牌  我孤助无援啊
I'm floating on the river here. Look at the table.
谁知道呢  我晚上带女朋友出去  这很花钱的
I don't know. I'm supposed to take my girl out later. It's a lot of money.
女朋友?  谁啊?
Your girl out? Who's that?
- 伊莱恩?  - 对
- Elaine? - Yeah.
你们在一起一阵子了
You guys have been going out for a while.
多久啦?
How long?
- 差不多两个月  - 不赖嘛!
- Couple months. - Couple months? Wow.
- 真不错  你们上床没?  - 算是吧
- That's big. You have sex with her yet? - Kinda.
- "算是吧"  是什么?  - "算是吧"?
- What the hell is "kinda"? - "Kinda"?
- 这个很隐私的事情  - 好吧  听仔细了
- Personal question. - Okay, well, listen.
告诉我们  今天晚上你们打算干嘛?
Let me ask you a question. What are you going to do tonight?
晚餐吃炸鱼片喝可乐?
Fish filet and a Coke?
然后去百视达租个浪漫喜剧片
Go to Blockbuster, rent a little romantic comedy,
然后到你老妈家坐沙发上看电视?
go back to Mom's house, sit on the couch?
- 你怎麽知道?  - 废话  你就会这些而已
- How'd you know? - Well, that's what you do.
因为你是个乖乖牌  所以你就会这些而已
You're a dependable person. That's what you're going to do.
- 你知道你该怎么办吗?
- You know what you should do? - Hmm?
你要好好的花笔钱  好好的款待你女友
You need to lay down some real green and treat your lady right.
你要带她去间高级餐厅
You know, you need to take her to a nice place.
红龙虾  橄榄园  来点轻音乐
Red Lobster. Olive Garden. Tablecloths. Soft music.
别看什么录影带了
And then you skip this Blockbuster thing.
女孩子喜欢外出  尤其像你那漂亮的女朋友
Girls want to go out. Especially a girl as cute as your girl, you know?
她打扮的漂漂亮亮就是要引人注目
She wants to be seen. That's why she dresses up.
所以你要带她去电影院
So you take her to the movies.
- 弄点爆米花饮料  - 说的对
- A little popcorn-drink combo. - True. True.
你也买点 伊莱恩 喜欢的热狗和玉米饼
Elaine might want a hot dog and some nachos, so you shell out for that, too.
然后当你心理还没准备好
And then before you know it,
她已经带你去她家里
she's cozying up the way she never would've
让你舒舒服服的
at her mom's house, you know?
- 说的好 - 突然之间
- Preach it. Preach it. - Now all of a sudden, look.
伊莱恩  已抓着高高站起的爱情罗密欧
Gino Romero's walking tall with Elaine yank-my-Dickinson,
- 如果你有种  这都是你的了  - 对  对
- all because he dared to dream tonight. - Yes! Yes! Yes!
做个男人吧  这是你的重大决定
And he became a man. And that's the choice.
- 对的  - 看看桌上这些
- Yes. - And that's what's on the table.
你的梦想就在这里
This is the dream right here.
你算是男人对吧?
Are you a man?
- 好吧  我跟了  - 太好了
- I'm with you. - Okay, here we go.
- 我下注 20.00  - 20.00
- I'm with you. 20? - 20.
好样的
Big boy game.
开牌吧
Call.
- 三条老K 大过你一对A  杰瑞 老大  - 漂亮
- Cowboys over aces, big Jer. - Wow. Wow.
- 没料到吧  - 不赖嘛
- Didn't see that coming, huh? - Yeah, that's a tough one.
看我的  四支A  瞧瞧
This is a tough one, too. Four bullets, baby.
混蛋  你忽悠我
Get out of here! You baited me into that, Jer. Come on!
- 这就是现实啊  - 那么我的红龙虾怎么办?
- That's the way it goes. - So what happened to Red Lobster?
没办法  你今晚只好回老妈家咯
No, I guess it's Mama's house for you tonight.
但是别难过  我省了你  40块钱
But look, I saved you 40 bucks.
而且  伊莱恩  也不需要看性病医生
And now Elaine won't have to shell out for herpes medication.
混蛋们  休息时间结束
Break's over, bitches.
费特安  没来上班
Freitag missed his shift again.
- 得有人做他的工作  - 妈的
- Someone's on collator duty. -  Great.
好吧  男士们
All right, well, gentlemen,
明天我们继续  你们回家玩得愉快
I'll give you a chance to win some of this back tomorrow. Enjoy yourselves.
明天见
All right, man.
你好  欢迎来到  复印小屋  需要帮忙吗
Hey there. Welcome to Copy Cabana. How can I help you?
那机器一直卡在主画面
I couldn't get the machine past the main menu.
- 那台机器?  - 对的
- That machine there? - Yeah.
先生  你用信用卡在左边刷过一次吗
Did you swipe your credit card to the left, sir?
- 没啊  - 那就是问题所在了
- Didn't do that. - Well, that's your problem.
再试试看吧
Why don't you try it again?
手机用户们  小心了
Cell phone users, beware.
联邦调查局  能知道你的一言一语
The Federal Bureau of Investigation can now hear everything you're saying,
甚至当你的手机是关机状态
even when your cell phone is turned off.
官方可以启动你的手机麦克风
Authorities can now activate the microphone inside your phone,
进一步窃听你所有的谈话
allowing them to eavesdrop on you and your conversations.
专家说唯一的办法就是把电池取出来
Experts say the only way around this is to take the battery out of the device.
死亡人数现在增加到 14 人
The death toll now stands at 14.
到达  联合大街
Now arriving at Union Street.
- 请不要靠近门口  - 抱歉
- Stand clear of the doors. - Excuse me.
请小心脚下
Watch your step, please.
这是你吗?
Did you drop this?
是的
Yes.
在地铁上画这个很不容易的
It's hard to do on a train, you know!
正在关门  请小心
Doors closing.
站立的客户请注意
Standing passengers...
- 拜托拜托  - 帐户余额不足
Come on, come on, come on.
杰瑞?
Jerry?
威兹堡斯基太太!  我...  我以为你还在睡觉
Mrs. Wierzbowski! I was just... I thought you might have been sleeping.
- 对对对 - 来  你看
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - So... But I have...
我这里有些房租
I have some rent here.
- 这些先给你  - 一些是不错  最好是能全部付清
- Here you go. - Yeah, some is good. All is better.
大部分都付了
Well, that's most of it. Here.
1美元...
$1, $1, $1...
看看  这里有个  5美元的
No, no, no. Look. Here's a five there.
- 5美元  - 对的
- Five. - Yeah.
你女朋友呢  好久没见到了
Where is girl? I don't see her no more.
你知道你是我的唯一嘛
You know you're the only woman for me.
结束了  她离开了
No, that's done. She got smart.
- 就像是其他女孩子  - 对的
- Like the others. - Yeah. Yeah.
女的嘛?  你接电话啊
Is woman friend? Answer.
看看她给不给你钱付房租
Then see if she give you money for rent.
不好意思  等一等
One second.
妈  什么事
Hey, Mom.
什么?
What?
- 看起来真像  - 我不是
- WO Looks just like him. - I'm not him.
- 六个月没声没息
Six months without a boo or a bah, huh?
是的
Yes, sir.
你最近哪里去了
So where were you this time?
阿拉斯加  新加坡  我在那里找了工作
Alaska. Singapore. I got a job there.
我跟史丹佛大学说了
I... I spoke to Stanford.
我找了些人
I pulled some strings.
他们愿意让你回去  虽然你之前退学了
They said they'd take you back. Even though you took off...
两年了  老爸
Two years ago, Dad.
杰瑞  找人帮忙不会要了你的命
Jerry, you know, it wouldn't kill you to ask for help once in a while.
你又要说教了吗
You want to have this conversation now?
- 那可是史丹佛 - 你非得在这个时候说吗
- It's Stanford! - You want to do this today.
你知道有多少人拼了命想进去...
You know how many people would kill...
- 你非要在这时候讲这些吗  - 好吧
- Today? You want to have this now? - Fine.
随便你了 你总是这样
You do whatever you want. You always have.
你知道吗  我希望有一天在这个家里
You know, I keep thinking, I'm going to walk in here one day
你能把我当自己儿子一样重视
and I'm not going to feel like a stranger in my own house.
我才不要你的钱
I don't want your money.
乘客请注意
Can I have your attention, please?
列车内是禁止吸烟的  下一站是芝加哥
Smoking is not permitted on the train. Chicago is next.
支票 1000美元
我找不到钥匙而且你老爸又迟到了
Can't find the keys and he's late as usual.
- 我得带你出发了  - 他会到的
- I'm going to have to take you. - He'll be here.
好吧  我们再等 5 分钟
All right, wait five more minutes.
来帮忙想  我们昨天回家很晚
Help me out here. We came home last night.
我把剩菜放下  你跑去开电视机  我过来
I put the leftovers down. You turned on the TV. I went over,
说  "不准看电视了"  关了电视机
said, "No TV, no TV, no TV." Turned it off.
到这里来  查看留言
Came over here. Checked the messages.
把电话弄掉了
Knocked over the phone.
对  弄掉了电话  又捡起来
Right, knocked over the phone. Put it back.
把剩菜放冰箱里
Put the leftovers in the fridge.
出发吧
Let's go!
维他命放在你的梳洗用具袋里  别忘记...
I put vitamins in your toiletry bag. Don't forget to take...
- 早晚各吃 2 粒  - 对的
- Two in the morning and two at night. - That's right.
你的哮喘呼吸器在你背包后面
And your inhaler's in the back of your bag.
- 小山姆!  - 爸爸!
- Sammy! - Daddy!
过来过来  我不会忘记来送你上车  对吧
Come here. You didn't think I'd miss the big send-off, do you, huh?
让我来带你上车
Let's get you on this train.
- 这一定是那个什么来着...  - 小喇叭
- This must be your... - Trumpet.
我的天啊  像有 200 磅那么重  你自己提得动吗
My God, this weighs, like, 200 pounds. You carry this yourself?
- 霍洛曼 先生和太太  - 女士
- Mr. And Mrs. Holloman! - Miss.
- 你差点来不及  - 差点
- You just made it. - Right.
- 山姆 过来  - 谢谢
- Here, Sam. - Thanks.
仔细听着
Listen to me
其他孩子都会给妈妈打电话  对吧
All these other kids, right? They're going to call their moms, too, all right?
他们不会老实交代吃了很多垃圾食品
They're just going to lie about it.
我能了解  但是记得好好刷牙
and eat junk food 'cause this is your one chance, but brush your teeth.
知道了 妈妈
Mom, you got to stop.
我会想你的
I'm going to miss you, too.
到国会大厦的准备出发
Capitol Limited to D.O. Is departing now.
来给我抱抱
Give me a hug.
全体上车
All aboard.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
- I love you so much. - I love you, too.
- 好好表现  - 好
- Shine bright, okay? - Okay.
- 小家伙准备震惊全场了  对吧
Rock the house, buddy. You're going to be great. Okay?
- 嗯  - 再见
- Okay. - I'll see you later.
- 再见!  - 在华盛顿玩得开心
- Bye! - CRAIG: Have fun in D. C!
- 妈妈再见  - 你妈妈没事吧
- GIRL: Bye, Mom! - Your mom going to be okay?
不太确定
It's unclear.
不好意思  路上塞车了
I'm so sorry. I got stuck in traffic,
- 而且我没有...  - 什么都别说
- and I didn't even... - Don't even say it.
全体上车!
All aboard!
是的  5-9-1-3
Yes. Five-nine-one-three.
没错  在这里
It's here. It's here.
知道了  好的
Okay, okay.
快点吧
WO Come on!
不好意思  马上好
Two seconds. Sorry.
75万1千美元
等等  有点不对
No, wait.
- 等等  - 不好意思
- Hey, hang on a second. - Sorry.
- 你的钱掉了 - 先生 先生
-  You're dropping money. - Sir, sir!
大日子  运气特别好
Big date, you know? Fingers crossed, huh?
- 这些你拿着  过得愉快  - 谢谢
- Here you go. Have a good day! - Thank you.
- 杰瑞!  - 什么?
- Oh, Jerry! - What?
- 一大堆盒子  - 盒子?
- So many boxes. - Boxes?
一整天不停地送来盒子  我只好打开你房间
I had to open your room. All day they come.
- 大大小小的盒子  - 送给我的?
- Big boxes, small boxes. - My boxes?
我不知道  但不给你会给谁的呢?
I don't know. Whose boxes would they be?
- 好吧  我看看  - 你自己看看  看到没?
- All right, okay. - Look at them there. See in there?
- 看  我全部放在...  - 好好  知道了
- See, I put them all... - Yeah. Yeah.
- 对了  这个先给你  - 什么
- Listen, I have something for you here. - Yeah.
这是这两个月的房租  没问题吧?
This is rent for this month and next month, too, okay?
- 我的天!  - 谢谢
- Oh, my. - Thank you.
喂?
Hello?
联邦调查局在  30  秒后会到达你的住所
WO The FBI will arrive at your apartment in 30 seconds.
马上离开这个房子
You must flee the premises.
谁...  是谁
Who... Who is this?
轮到你加入行动了  杰瑞
You've been activated, Jerry.
-到底谁  -你必须服从
- Who the hell is this? - Your compliance is vital.
你怎么知道这个电话的
How did you get this number?
你还有24秒  离开这个房子
You now have 24 seconds. Leave your residence.
先到玛西斯火车站  在那会给你指令
Your destination, the Mathis train station. We will guide you from there.
这是什么
What is this?
你房里证据确凿
The evidence in your apartment is irrefutable.
-听着  -17秒
- Listen. - 17 seconds.
我要挂电话了
I'm going to hang this phone up now.
他们将会以共谋叛国罪逮捕你
They'll seek your arrest for conspiracy, treason...
-我要挂电话了  违反国家地区法律
- I'm hanging this phone up now! ...violating state and local law.
-你告诉我你怎么知道这个电话的  -最大的惩罚  死
- You tell me how you got this number! - Maximum penalty, death.
不  这些东西都不是我的
No, none of this is mine!
联邦调查局  趴在地上
FBI, FBI, FBI! Get down on the floor!
趴在地上
Get on the ground!
快点  趴下
Down now! Get down!
-我什么都没干  -趴下
- I didn't do anything! - Get down!
-听我说  -不许动
- Listen! - Don't move.
那不是我的  不是我的
It's not mine! It's not mine!
这肯定搞错了 对吧
This is obviously some sort of mistake, right?
长官  我不明白为什么来这
I mean, I don't know what I'm doing in this room, sir.
外面冷极了
It's cold as hell outside.
-你画画吗  -什么
- You draw? - I what?
你画画吗  素描  你手指上都是墨汁
Do you draw? Do you sketch? You have ink all over your fingers.
瞧  你们抓错人了 是吧
Look, you know you got the wrong guy, right?
这一定是恶作剧
I mean, this is all some kind of sick joke.
-我不知道我在这干嘛  -很显然
- I don't know what I'm doing here. - Obviously.
很明显这些跟你没什么关系
Obviously you have nothing to do with it, yeah.
你爱你哥哥吗
Did you love your brother?
或者你狠他吗  你崇拜他吗
Or did you hate him? Did you admire him?
你哥哥爱国吗
Was your brother patriotic, would you say?
你最后一次见到他是什么时候
When's the last time you saw him?
-圣诞节  -刚刚过去的圣诞节
- Christmas. - This past Christmas?
-三年前的圣诞节  -三年
- Three Christmases ago. - Three years, huh?
可是电话记录显示
Well, the phone records show
你已经有一年没有给他打过电话了
that you haven't even called him in over a year.
没有文字信息  没任何联系
So no text messages? No smoke signals?
没有网站留言
No MySpace or Facebook messages?
是的  你想说什么  我们没有...
Yeah, so what are you trying to say? We're not...
你是不是想说我们是那种双胞胎
Are you asking if we’re the type of twins
穿着同样的T恤逛商场  手拉着手
that wear the same shirt to the mall, hold hands
或者类似的事情  不
and things like that? No.
先生  我还不知道你的名字
Sir, I don't even know your name.
对不起  我的错
I'm sorry, that was rude of me.
我叫汤姆 摩根
I'm Tom Morgan,
联合反恐特种部队的检察官
the Supervising Agent assigned to the Joint Terrorism Task Force.
恐...
Ter...
你觉得我是个恐怖分子
You think I'm a terrorist?
不  你是个打印小工  对吗
No, you're a copy boy, aren't you?
我是个复印合伙人
I'm a copy associate.
复印合伙人
Copy associate.
但是你哥哥
But your brother,
他是个比你有野心的人
it says here he was a little more, I guess you'd say, ambitious than you.
21岁从空军军官学校毕业
Graduated from the Air Force Academy at 21,
获得了并行算法和量子物理学学位
with an advanced degree in parallel algorithms and quantum electronics.
我不知道这到底意味着什么  你知道吗
I don't even know what the hell that stuff means. Do you?
中校实习生  优秀毕业生  就职在公共事务...
Cadet wing commander, valedictorian, plum job in the Public Affairs...
是的  别说了  我知道他的事
Yeah, no, I know what he did, sir.
你为什么退学  杰瑞
Why'd you drop out of school, Jerry?
你哥哥对你做这个决定有什么影响吗
Did your brother have any influence on that decision?
没有  我不适合学校
No, school just wasn't for me.
不会吧  谁不想上斯坦福大学
No, I mean, who would want a Stanford education anyway?
难道在复印小屋更有前途
More upward mobility at Copy Cabana, I guess, right?
我知道你旅行  新加坡  巴厘岛  印度尼西亚
I see you did a little backpacking. Singapore, Bali, Indonesia.
四处打工  就像现在这份工作
Did odd jobs here and there. So you've been around.
这些都跟在我公寓的那些他妈的东西
Look, none of this has anything to do
没有任何关系
with any of the shit that was in my apartment.
我干嘛把这些东西寄给自己
Why would I send it to myself?
我的名字就在合约上
My name is on the lease.
我可能是这世上最蠢的恐怖分子了
I'd have to be the dumbest terrorist in the history of the world.
那是谁存了这75万
So who deposited the 750?
这...  我不知道谁存的
The... I don't know who deposited the 750!
可能是上帝吧  我想这是个奇迹吧
God maybe? I thought it was a miracle,
我拿了钱  这是我的错  这是个意外
I took the money. That was my mistake. It was an accident.
你从来没发生过意外吗
Do accidents not happen in your universe?
好吧  这些钱来自新加坡银滩银行
Well, the money originated from the YTBC Bank of...
真让我惊讶
Well, I'll be darned, Singapore.
是一个叫猎户之星的公司转的帐
Opened with a transfer from a corporation called The Star of Orion,
-真主党的假前身  -这些很趣  先生
- a dummy front for Hezbollah. - This is all very interesting, sir.
-我什么都没做  -我们在你的房间里找到了装备
- It has nothing to do with me. - We find hardware in your apartment.
最新的军事细则
Latest military spec.
-空军手册  -我已经跟你说了
- Airplane manuals. - I told you about this already.
还有1200磅的硝酸铵化肥
And 1,200 pounds of ammonium nitrate fertilizer.
我走进我的房子
I walked into my apartment...
你想当个农民还是什么
You planning on becoming a farmer or something?
我走进我的房子  打开门
I walk into my apartment, I open the door,
这些东西就他妈的在我的房里了
and this shit's all over my apartment.
-它们自己出来的  -它们自己在那的
- It just showed up. - It just showed up.
我明白了  我只是好奇你的哥哥知不知道这件事
I see. I'm just curious if your brother knew anything about it.
对了  我们还不知道你们俩是怎么联系的  对吗
Of course, we haven't really established how close you guys were yet, have we?
今天早上我把他埋在地底下的时候见过
Well, we were pretty close this morning when I buried his body in the ground.
这回你知道了吧  有人陷害我
Does that establish anything for you? Somebody set me up.
你怎么就不明白呢
Why is that so hard for you to understand?
-有人  -一个女人给我打电话
- "Somebody." - A woman called me on the phone.
她告诉我要被抓了
She told me I was going to be arrested.
一个女人  你妈吗  谁
"A woman." Your mom? Who?
我不知道  要是我知道我就告诉你了
I don't know!If I knew,I would tell you!
我不知道
I don't know!
就是这样  杰瑞
Here's the thing, Jerry.
恐怖分子现在特别受到  "重视"
This is a bad time to be in the terrorism business.
你看过这张报纸
You read the paper.
你觉得谁会赢了
Who do you think is winning?
我想让你在呆多久就呆多久
to keep you in this room as long as I want to?
你不关心你把你哥哥的事告诉我
I don't care if you tell me the truth about your brother.
不关心你为谁工作
I don't care who you work for.
因为不管你告诉我什么
'Cause no matter what you tell me
你都有一大堆麻烦  小子
you're in a shitload of trouble, son.
这太荒唐了  我在出版小屋工作
This is insane. I work for Copy Cabana.
是啊  你说过了
Yeah, that's what you said.
知道吗  我有十年没晚上出来玩了
Listen, I get one night out in a decade, ladies,
今晚想玩个痛快
I am not wasting it on Lemon Drops.
-好的  -来吧
- Okay. - Buck up. Let's go.
我要改头换面  斗斗嘴  找个伴
I want updates. Catfights, booty calls
有人说他们能带来好运
somebody tell me they got lucky.
女士们  看到那边的那个小伙了吗
Hey, ladies. See that guy over there?
他想请你喝一杯
He'd like to buy you a round.
不
Hell, no.
他有的是淡啤
He's got light beer written all over him.
-他很可爱  -拜托
- He's cute. - Come on.
他在求爱  不行
- He's a suit. No.
你确定
You sure?
-行了  -是谁
Come on. FRIEND 2: Who is it?
是这个世上唯一没让我失望的男人
The one man in my life who hasn't let me down.
真温馨
Aww. That's sweet.
好了  等我一起喝
All right, don't drink those without me.
喂
Hello?
在街对面有一个麦当劳   看看橱窗
WO There's a McDonald's across the street. Look in the window.
什么
What is this?
你愿意为你的儿子冒险吗
Would you risk your life for your son?
瑞秋 霍洛曼  到你加入行动了
Rachel Holloman, you've been activated.
开什么玩笑
This isn't funny.
你的服从至关重要
Your compliance is vital.
-你是谁  -我们将会让他的火车脱轨
- Who are you? - We will derail his train,
除非你照我们说的去做
unless you do what you're told.
做什么
What is this?
别回饭店
Don't go back inside the restaurant.
-什么  -在这个街区的东北角
- What? - There's a black Porsche Cayenne
停着一辆黑色的保时捷凯宴
parked at the northeast corner of this block.
钥匙在点火器上  行动吧
The keys are in the ignition. Start walking.
天啊
Oh, my God.
这里是911报警处
911. State the nature of your emergency.
刚才我接到一个女人的电话
Yeah, some woman just called me.
我...  我不知道她是谁
I have... I have no idea who she is.
她告诉我...
She was telling me that...
你的电话被监控了
WO Your phone is being monitored.
再违抗命令  你的儿子就没命了
Disobey again and your son dies.
格兰特  我读不了肖文件
Hey, Grant, I can't read this Shaw file.
-格兰特  -失陪下
- Grant! - Excuse me.
我的眼睛一直都不好
Listen, my eyes aren't getting any better
这屏幕太小了
and these screens are getting smaller.
你能找个让我能看的清东西吗
Could you please find me something I can read?
我让这些字大一些
I can make the text bigger on your screen.
不不不  我是在说纸的文件
No, no, no. I'm talking about paper.
记住  就跟过去一样
Remember, like in the olden times?
-纸的  好的  -好的
- Paper. Okay. - Yeah.
摩根探长  佐伊 佩雷  空军特别调查员
Agent Morgan. Zoe Perez, Air Force Special Investigations.
伊森.肖是我们空军的 他们是双胞胎
Ethan Shaw, the twin, he was one of ours.
网络检测显示他们一直在联系
Yeah. OSI said they were sending a liaison.
能边走边说吗
Can you walk and talk at the same time?
我尽量
I'll do my best.
文件说他在一次交通事故中丧生
File says he died in a traffic accident.
在华盛顿被闯了红灯的卡车撞了
Truck ran a light, corner of Constitution and 10th, Northwest D.C.
卡车闯红灯  他弟弟就能得75万和一大堆装备
So truck ran a light, his brother gets 750 large and enough hardware
他要开超市吗
to start his own Costco,
就发生在恐怖袭击后的五小时
five hours after enemy chatter hits the roof.
你不觉得这有点太巧了吗
I mean, don't you find that a little coincidental?
这会不会是个诱饵  转移我们的视线
What if it's a decoy? To distract us from something 50 times bigger.
美国司法部长办公室
UNITED STATES ATTORNEY GENERAL'S OFFICE
授权
authorize
Jerry Shaw
打电话
phone call
-你可以打电话了  -我记的不能电话的
- Time for your phone call. - I thought I didn't get one.
检查院改变注意了
Attorney General's office changed their mind.
伊森 肖 智商183
Ethan Shaw had a 183 IQ
你觉得他是个二流炮兵
and yet you had him as a mid-level press flak.
为什么不是计算机网络战争
Why not IT or cyber-warfare?
你是说他聪明过头了
Are you suggesting that he was overqualified?
还是说他在复印小屋偷偷的上网
Or that he was somehow slipping intel to the Copy Cabana?
不  我是说伊森 肖
No, I'm suggesting that maybe Ethan Shaw
可能是个犯了错的超级火箭科学家天才
was a superstar rocket scientist genius who did go wrong,
空军部队让人知道他们的丑事
and the Air Force doesn’t want their dirty laundry flapping in the wind.
随便你  但是我要自己进去审问他
Think what you like, but I need to get in that room and interrogate him myself.
不
No.
你没得选 这样吧...
You don't have a choice. Look.
跳下去  杰瑞 肖
JUMP JERRY SHAW
现在我们并不知道他们有没有罪
Now, neither of us know if either of those brothers are guilty or innocent,
我代表空军部长  我要参加审问
so on behalf of the Secretary of the Air Force, I'm going in that room.
好吧  我代表那小子房子里
Well, on behalf of all that fucking bomb equipment
所有的炸弹  不  你不能进去
in junior pinhead's apartment, no, you're not.
告诉过你快跑  那是计划好的
WO We told you to run. We have planned your escape.
你怎么接通这个电话的  你是谁
How'd you get on this phone? Who are you?
马上趴在地上
Lay flat on the floor immediately.
什么  你到底在说什么
What the... What the hell are you talking about?
4秒  杰瑞
Four seconds, Jerry.
-不  你他妈胡说什么  我不...
- No, this is bullshit. I don't...
马上趴下
Get down now.
2秒
Two seconds.
杰瑞 快跳
不
No!
是的  杰瑞 跳
YES,JERRY JUMP
-不  这不是我干的  -趴下
- No! I didn't do this! - Get down!
妈的
Shit.
杰瑞 上火车
JERRY BOARD THE TRAIN
旅客同志们
Standing passengers,
请不要靠在门旁边
please do not lean against the doors.
14个美国人死亡
fourteen Americans dead
恐怖组织坚称
Throughout Europe and the Middle East,
针对由西方挑起的欧洲和中东的战争
with terror groups insisting this is just the beginning
才刚刚开始
of a campaign the West invited when it allegedly rained bombs
当他们在阿富汗边缘Abda的小镇外的
on a religious ceremony outside the small town of Abda,
宗教典礼上投炸弹时战争就开始了
near the border of Afghanistan.
坐火车经过三个站
WO Stay on the train for three more stations
然后在站台等着
and wait at the bottom of the platform.
你会收到...
You will receive...
门要关了
Doors closing.
乘客们  请不要靠在门边
Standing passengers, please do not lean against the doors.
帮帮我  Jimmy  我的孩子
Help! WO Jimmy. My baby.
谁帮帮我啊
I need some help. Somebody.
-什么  -你没听到吗
- What? - WO You're not listening.
我叫你留在火车上
We told you to stay on the train.
-你怎么做到的  -下一站是Wilson车站
- How are you doing this? - Next stop is Wilson Station.
在西北出口有一辆黑色的保时捷凯宴等你
A black Porsche Cayenne will be waiting at the northwest exit.
-听着  -坐在座位上
- Listen. - Get in the passenger seat.
听着  不  我不干了
Listen! No, I'm done.
喂
Hello?
安全门前
WO The man in front of the exit door
穿黑夹克的男子是恐怖分子
in a black coat is a wanted terrorist.
-他的名字叫杰瑞 肖  -谁啊
- His name is Jerry Shaw. -  Who is this?
-你是杰瑞 肖吗  -不对
- You Jerry Shaw? - No, no, no.
Wilson站到了  请下车
Wilson Station. Exit now.
是那个人
That's the guy!
我问你是杰瑞·肖吗  过来
I said, are you Jerry Shaw? Hey! Come here!
小心
Watch it!
-开车  快开车  -不
- Drive the car! Drive the car! - No!
-我照你说的做了  -我哪都不想去
- I did what you asked me to! - I'm not going anywhere...
-你告诉我...  停下来...  直到你告诉我我的儿子没事
- You tell... Stop! ...until you tell me my son's safe!
谁是你的儿子  我不知道你在说什么
Who's your son? I don't know what you're talking about!
-你要是伤害我的儿子我就杀了你
- I'll kill you if you hurt my son!
我他妈的已经快死了
I almost died over this shit!
-你听我说  我不知道你...  -告诉我山姆没事
- Listen, lady, I don't know who... - Tell me Sam is safe!
谁是...  你别打了行吗
Who is... Will you stop hitting me?
你是给我打电话的那个女人吗
Are you the woman who called me on the phone?
-你给我打过电话吗  -没有  那个女人
- Did you call me on the phone? - No. The woman.
-她也给你打了  -她也给你打了
- She called you, too? - She called you, too?
开车
Drive.
下车  快点下车
Get out! Now! Get out of the vehicle!
停车
Stop!
-这到底是怎么回事  -快  快走
- Why is this happening? - Go, go, go, go, go!
你是谁  为什么有人朝我们开枪
Who are you and why are people shooting at us?
开车  踩油门
Drive the car! Clutch!
加速行驶  右转  200米  你被跟踪了
Accelerate. Turn right, 200 feet. You have pursuers.
-妈的  你到底是谁  -不要问问题
- Yeah, no shit! Who are you? - No questions.
现在右转
Turn right now.
那你不知道山姆怎样了
So you don't know anything about Sam?
什么  你说你儿子  不  我什么都不知道
What, you mean your son? No, I know nothing.
就像你不知道怎么开车一样
Just like you don't know how to drive.
转弯前踩油门  转弯的时候别踩
Use the clutch before you shift, not while you shift!
用不着你教我  混蛋
I don't need driving lessons from you, asshole!
什么  你这样开车  还说我是傻帽
What, you drive like this and I'm the asshole?
现在左转
Turn left now.
所有部门注意  驾驶着保时捷的嫌疑犯
All units. Suspect in a Porsche Cayenne
在格兰街向西行驶
heading west on Grand.
-各部门请回应  号码3  -在那
- All units respond, Code 3. - There!
保持50码的速度
Maintain a speed of 50 miles an hour.
保持在右侧二道
Stay in the second lane from the right.
-红灯了  -加速
- The light's red! - Accelerate now.
在格兰维尔和谢里登路口设路障
Get me a roadblock at Granville and Sheridan.
妈的
Oh, shit.
所有的灯都变绿了
The lights are all turning green.
老天啊
Holy shit!
-上帝啊
- Holy... - Shit!
再近点
Get in close.
快快快
Go, go, go!
妈的
Shit!
刹车  刹车
Brake. Brake now.
从这里进来
Get in here!
加速到每小时60英里
Accelerate to 60 miles per hour.
离合器  离合器
Clutch. Clutch!
-踩离合器  -在踩啊
- Use the clutch! - I'm clutching!
我看着呢  你没踩
I'm watching, you're not clutching!
-停车  -我不会那样做
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Stop! - I'm not stopping.
慢点  前面是红灯
Slow down. Slow down, the light's red.
不要减速  加速到每小时72英里
Don't slow down. Accelerate to 72 miles per hour.
-减速  是红灯  -你会开过去的
- Slow down. It's a red light! - You will make it through.
-停住  -不行
- Stop! - No way.
-刹车  -我不能
- Brake! - I can't!
刹车
Brake!
停住
Stop!
恢复手动控制
Manual control's been restored.
笔直开到15号码头
Continue straight until you reach Pier 15.
进入打捞场  再到码头尽头
Enter the wrecking yard. Proceed to the end of the dock.
我们会排除一切障碍
We will eliminate all obstacles for you.
小心
Watch! Watch! Watch!
稳住
Stay your course.
转弯
Turn!
-拐弯  -现在
- Turn! - Turn right now.
-抓住座椅  -我不行
- Grab the seat. - I can't.
- Grab the seat! The seat! - No, I can't!
起重机要放开车子了
The crane will release the car.
如果不跳  你们就会淹死
If you do not jump, you will drown.
-必须得跳  -不  不要
- We have to jump. - No! No way.
必须跳  等我说跳
We have to. When I say "go."
预备
Ready?
跳
Go! Jump!
落水的两个都给找出来
I want both the divers in that water!
-走吧  行动  -开始吧  行动
- Let's go! Move! -Let's go, let's go!
行动
Move, move, move!
对  我已经提上来了
Yeah, I already called it in!
等没人了再放下去
Wait till it clears!
退后30英尺  就这样
30 feet back, that's it!
我知道  部队派了一架黑鹰
Yeah, I know, the Army sent a Black Hawk,
我两小时内到
so I'll be there in a couple of hours.
什么意思  车子没登记
What do you mean, the car is not registered to anyone?
再检查一遍号码
Check the VIN number again.
给山姆留言吧
Leave your message for Sam,
虽然我知道是你  妈妈
even though I know it's you, Mom.
山姆  宝贝  听我说
Sam? Baby, listen to me.
收到消息后立刻给我电话  好吗
You need to call me as soon as you get this message, okay?
记住了  宝贝  我爱你
Baby, please. I love you.
-那个女的呢?  -什么
- MORGAN: What about the girl? - What?
找到那个女的没
What about the girl?
交通部说交通摄像机
Well, the Department of Transpo tells me that there was
出现了7分钟的设备故障
a seven-minute equipment failure on their traffic cams.
-没有拍到她  -有没有搞错
- We didn't get a picture of her. - Don't tell me that.
-他们就这么和我说的  -我要那女人的身份
- That's what they're telling me! - I need an ID on that girl.
你觉得他们能让火车脱轨吗
Do you think they could derail a train?
他们把红绿灯都变了
They changed every traffic light to get us here.
那个女人  打给刚好坐我边上的
The woman, she called me on a stranger's cell phone
一个陌生人  我从没见过他
who happened to be sitting next to me. Never met the guy in my life.
接着把我从戒备最森严的警局
You know, and then they broke me out of maximum security custody
弄了出来  你不知道那有多疯狂
in a way I'm not even gonna describe to you because it sounds crazy,
然后把我们提起来扔进垃圾堆里
and then they lift us off the face of the Earth and drop us into this shit pile?
她肯定能火车脱轨
She could probably derail a train.
甚至把火车变成会说话的鸭子
She could probably turn a train into a talking duck.
那些帮他们逃生的
And what about these goddamn ghost cranes
该死的起重机怎么说呢
that keep helping peewee out?
他们不可能像两根巨大的筷子
I mean, they don’t just lift cars up in the air all by themselves
自动把车提起来
like a giant pair of chopsticks.
我想知道他们怎么工作的
I want to know how these things run, how they're programmed.
你叫什么来着
What'd you say your name was?
-瑞秋  -我是杰瑞
- Rachel. - I'm Jerry.
你好
Hello?
游艇14分钟内就到
WO The barge will dock in 14 minutes.
离开修船厂  上123号公路往东走
Leave the boatyard with the female. Take Highway 123 East.
走到路标108
Walk to mile marker 108.
-是她吗  -她叫你"那个女的"
- What? Was it her? - She called you "the female."
让后勤部冻结伊森·肖所有东西
Have Mortuary Affairs freeze everything belonging to Ethan Shaw.
-不留下任何随身物品  -喂  正当程序
- No personal effects to next of kin. - You, Due Process!
-再见  -有伊森 肖的消息吗
- Bye. - What do you have on Ethan Shaw?
有个名字  佩雷特工
I have a name. It's Agent Perez.
从华盛顿回来我再回答你
And I'll answer that question when I get back from D.C.
-等等  那里有什么线索  -肖的私人住处
- Wait a minute. What's in D. C? - Shaw's private quarters.
你不能走  我不能失去伊森·肖的线索
I need you to stay here. I'm not losing my link to Ethan Shaw.
也许我还没说清楚  我不是替你干活
Maybe I haven't made this clear. I don't work for you.
我为空军干活
I work for the Air Force.
别关机  我会及时告诉你
Keep your phone on, I'll keep you updated.
别盯着我  我又不是疑犯
If you're staring at me, it better be because I'm the goddamn suspect.
如果我得不到线索  你们都要降职
Because if I don't get some good leads soon, you're all gonna be demoted
去干脏活
into something that's gonna require touching shit with your hands.
去吧  有活要干
Now, let's get going. We got work to do.
环已烷  最新的化学炸弹
Hexamethylene. Our latest chemical explosive.
一颗小水晶  比C4强80倍
One single tiny crystal, 80 times more powerful than C4.
无味  隐形
Odorless, undetectable.
最好的是  能切成小块用做秘密行动
And best of all, it can be cut down in size for stealth operations.
这是声控引爆器
This valve is a sonic trigger.
声频引发爆炸
The sound frequency triggers the explosion.
每个触发器都有独特的频率
Each trigger is programmed to have a unique frequency
都对应唯一的水晶
specific only to one Hex crystal.
由那个声频触发爆炸
That frequency triggers the explosion.
最近得到批准
We recently received approval
可以投入实战了
to begin shipping to the field.
今天已经出厂200个
Two hundred units are shipping out today.
-在这签字  -好
- Sign right here. -  Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
你接到的包裹里有个小金属管
WO The package you've just received contains a small metal valve.
打开包裹
Open the package.
-好的  -去掉阀门
- Okay. - Remove the valve
-仔细听我们的指令
- and follow our instructions precisely.
-你接到了包裹  -是的  刚到
- You've received the package. - Yes, ma'am, it just arrived.
-这是什么石头  -别提问
- What kind of stone is this? - No questions.
切开石头  按我们发给你的
Cut the stone and place the setting
说明书装置好
according to the specifications we sent you.
我刚送完我儿子上火车
I'd just dropped my son off at the train.
电话来时正在和朋友喝酒
I was out having drinks with my girlfriends when the call came.
你呢
What about you?
第一个电话打到我公寓
The first call came to my apartment.
-在盒子寄来后  -对
- After the boxes? - Yeah.
显然和你哥有关
Well, then this whole thing's obviously gotta be about your brother.
-是吗  有那么明显  -我是说  那么多东西
- Really, it's that obvious, huh? - I mean, you got all this stuff.
武器  钱  飞行手册
The weapons, the cash, the airplane manuals.
-好的  -他是你哥
- Okay. - He was your twin.
-他们送错人了  -对
- They sent it to the wrong brother. - Right.
你是说我哥是恐怖分子
So you're implying my brother's a terrorist.
如果他不是  为什么你是
I'm implying, if not him, then why you?
抱歉 我没要在他刚过世时破坏其名声
I'm sorry. I know he just died. I'm not trying to insult his memory or anything.
没有  他还没成往事  瑞秋
No, he hasn't been dead long enough to be a memory, Rachel.
如果你认识我哥哥  听到他是个恐怖分子
If you knew my brother, you'd laugh all day at the idea
或间谍  你会笑趴下
that he was a terrorist or a spy or whatever else you're saying...
-你怎么知道  -因为我是他弟
- How do you know? - Because he's my brother.
这点应该清楚
That's something you would know about your brother.
好吧  你上次见他是什么时候
Well, when's the last time you talked to him?
我不需要这些  没必要向你解释
I don't need this. Hey, listen. Hey! I don't have to explain myself to you.
-你儿子是恐怖分子  -是的
- Is your son a terrorist? - Yeah, my son's a terrorist.
他和我哥一样很可能是恐怖分子
Yeah, well, he's just as likely to be a terrorist as my brother.
你也在这  你为什么在这儿  你干什么的
And let's not forget you in all this. Why are you here? What's your day job?
-我知道你不是个开车的  -我是助理律师
- I know it isn't manual shift driver. - I'm a paralegal.
-这都与我无关  -助理律师
- I don't have a connection to anything. - Paralegal?
我怎么知道你没撒谎  助理是做什么的
How do I know you're not lying to me? What does a paralegal do?
和那些门上有自己名字的人一样
The same thing as the guys with their names on the door,
只不过我每小时11块  而他们能赚200块
except I do it for $11 an hour, so they can bill 200.
这说的过去吧  侦探
That nail it for you, Sherlock?
还是搞不懂我们为啥会在这
That still doesn't explain why we're walking out here...
-我可不知道  -我知道
- I don't know why the hell I'm out here! - Yeah, I know...
-你是杰瑞·肖  -你是谁
- Are you Jerry Shaw? - Who are you?
-等等  -我照她说的送包裹来了
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. - I sent the package like she asked.
-慢着  什么包裹  -那是什么
- Wait, what package? - What is that?
-现在她让我载你  -她?
- Now she wants me to drive you? -  Who, "she"?
-我不干  我不干了  -你认识她?
- I won't. I'm done! - You know "she"?
-等等   -在那别动
Wait.  Stay right there.
-回来  -这儿是地址
- Get back. - Here. Here's the address.
你为什么攻击  钥匙
Why are you attack... Here. Here are the keys.
把车开走
Take the goddamn van!
-你以为  -这是谁干的
- You think I'm going to... - Who's doing this?
因为我是伊朗人?  我是美国人  我不干了
...do this because I'm Iranian? I am American. I'm finished! I'm done!
-等一下  你在说什么  -拿着
- What? What are you talking about? - You take it!
-你在说什么  -我不会做了 因为我不能
- What are you talking about? - I won't do this because I can't.
-喂  -拦住他  否则他会死
- Hello? - WO Stop him now, or he will die.
听我说  你在说什么
Listen to me, what are you talking about?
-你们自己开车吧  -你怎么看得见我们
- You try to do this without me! - How are you seeing us right now?
-现在让他停住  -她在说什么
- Stop him now. - What is she saying?
-站住  你必须停下来  -等等
- Stop. Hey! You gotta stop! - Wait!
站住
You gotta stop!
-你杀了他  -谁都不能逃跑
- You killed that man. - WO Desertion is not an option.
开车去印第安纳波利斯
Take the van. Drive to Indianapolis, Indiana.
西56大街72号  11点前必须赶到
72 West 56th Street. Arrive no later than 11:00 a.m.
-欢迎  - 佩雷探员
- Welcome. - Hello. Agent Perez.
-右边  -对  女士
- To the right? - Yes, ma'am.
-身份证  女士  -空军特别调查处
- ID, ma'am. - OSI.
我下令冻结伊森·肖的财产  这是怎么回事
I ordered a freeze on Ethan Shaw's personal effects. What's going on?
少校下令要大扫除
Orders to sanitize came down from the Two Star.
好吧  我收回那个命令  谢谢你们  我来接手
Okay, I'm countermanding. Thank you. I'll take that.
-叫你的人先撤  -你是谁
- Tell your guys to clear out. - Who are you?
这个现场属于联邦调查的范围
This scene's part of a federal investigation
关系到国家安全  这是你的记录
with national security ramifications. This your log?
-是的  -好的  我是 佩雷特工
- Yes, it is. - Okay, my name is Agent Perez.
拿着这个和你上司上去
You can take this up with your superiors.
-出去吧  -你们出去
- Clear the room! - You guys move out.
没戴手套  给每个人做口录
No gloves? Get statements from everybody.
-是  女士  -找出是哪位少校
- Yes, ma'am. - And find out who this Two Star is.
我是说  赶紧
I mean, come on, really!
长官  找到身份了
Sir! We have a positive ID.
皮都烧坏了  可还是提取了部分指纹
The skin was pretty fried, but we still managed to get
是瑞尼 科里得
a partial print that matches to a Ranim Khalid.
他是美国公民  共和党人  开了一家音乐商店
He's a United States citizen, registered Republican, and he owns a music store.
-这家伙背景很干净  -找到了这个
- The guy's cleaner than Ivory Snow. - Got something here.
-是个石头麦克风  -喂
-That's a bone mic. - Hello.
军用级别的  肯定不是在eBay上买的
Military grade. He didn't get that on eBay.
有人在和他说话
Someone was talking to him.
有个网络恐怖分子
We have a cyber-terrorist here.
已经进入了我们的电脑系统
Someone's already inside our computer systems,
控制了电网  交通摄像机  自动起重机
hacking into the power grid, traffic cams, automated cranes.
那两个人肯定有帮凶
There's no way the boy and the girl did this alone.
请输入用户名
错误
佐伊 佩雷探员
Agent Zoe Perez?
-是  -美国空军安全部队
- Yes. - United States Air Force Security Forces.
请跟我们来
Please come with us.
-这是什么意思  -上车
- What's this about? - Get in the car.
中东地区爆发了暴力活动
Violence has broken out in the Middle East
好战分子谴责美方用导弹
as militants accuse the United States of launching American missiles
袭击俾路支的一个村庄  杀死无辜居民
to demolish a village in Baluchistan, killing innocent civilians.
这次袭击引发了一系列对美国使馆的
The attack has triggered a series of retaliatory suicide bombings
报复性自杀爆炸行为
against American embassies abroad.
早期报导显示死亡数已达到56人
Early reports indicate the American death toll now stands at 56,
本土可能遭受更多的暴力威胁
with threats of further violence here at home.
官员们
Officials...
你儿子在火车上干嘛
What's he doing on a train, your kid?
去音乐中心
He goes to a music magnet.
他们到华盛顿旅游  要去肯尼迪中心表演
His school's on a tour of Washington. They're playing at the Kennedy Center.
哇  很不错啊  你
Wow. That's big. And you just...
你为什么"哼"
Well, why'd you make that noise, "Huh"?
我不能那样说话吗
I can't make noises now?
-你认为我也该去  -他在肯尼迪中心表演
- You think I should have gone. - He's playing at the Kennedy Center.
-有点牛啊  -是的
- That's kind of a big deal. - It is a big deal.
所以我认为家长该去一个
So I think maybe one parent should have gone, that's all I'm saying.
一个要工作  另一个千方百计
Well, one parent had to work while the other one does
逃避抚养的责任
everything humanly possible to bail on child support.
我不觉得你是个有责任感的人
But I don't expect you to know a thing about responsibility.
瑞秋  你可一点都不了解我
You know, Rachel, you don't know the first thing about me.
我知道你哥刚死了
I know your brother just died,
他让我的孩子陷入危险
and whatever he was into put my son's life at risk.
我不想谈论我哥  好吗  说真的
I don't wanna talk about my brother. Okay?I'm not kidding.
我也是
I'm not kidding, either.
天啊  都发生什么了
Jesus, look what happened.
你能说他与此无关吗
Can you honestly say he had nothing to do with this?
我请你不要谈论他  尊重这一点
I'm asking you not to talk about him! Respect that.
我请你坦率地面对自己  你哥哥
I'm asking you to be honest with yourself. Your brother's a...
你不能就这么走了
Hey! You can’t just walk away! You can’t just leave!
-我能  -现在我们有15分钟
- Yes, I can. - Now we have 15 minutes to get
-到那儿  对吗  -是的
- wherever the hell we're going, all right? - Yeah.
我需要你
I need you.
我要去
I could've gone.
我该去
I should have.
你们慢了两分钟
WO You are two minutes behind schedule.
去大楼后的小巷
Go to the alley behind the building.
-到装甲车那  -没看到
- Go to the armored truck. - I don't see an armored truck.
在那
There it is.
20秒内  会有人走出电梯  都带了枪
WO In 20 seconds, men will exit the elevator. They will be armed.
一个提着公文包
One will be carrying a briefcase.
把包抢过来放到车上
Retrieve it from him, then return to the van.
-太可怕了  我不干  -你要我们抢劫
- This is insane. I'm not doing this. - You want us to rob them?
还有15秒
WO You now have 15 seconds.
保安  什么情况
Security. What's your emergency?
你在干吗  我没抢劫
What are you doing? I'm not robbing them. Shit.
枪放地上
Put your gun on the floor.
枪放地上  往前看
Put your gun on the floor! Look straight.
要我爆了他吗  枪放地上
You want me to blow his head off? Put the gun on the ground!
我们不想伤害你  放下包
We don't wanna hurt you guys. Just drop the case.
放下包然后踢给她
Drop the case and kick it to her!
你们的麻烦可大了
Yeah, well, you're bringing a shit storm on your head.
我们已经有一堆麻烦  现在把箱子踢过去
Yeah, we're already in mid shit storm! Now kick the case.
好的  放松点
Okay! Easy.
-看着前面  -好了
- Look straight. - Okay, done.
踢过去
Kick it!
-想都别想  -后退
- Don't even think about it! - Back up.
放松点
Easy.
后退
Back up.
到那去  和他站一起  转过去
Walk over here, stand next to him, and turn around.
-站过来  -放松点
- Stand over here! - Just take it easy.
转过去  转过去  转过去
Turn around. Turn around. Turn around!
快  快
Let's move, let's move!
快走
Come on!
杰瑞  给你
Jerry! Here!
让开  让开
Move, move!
警察  不许动
Freeze! Police!
把枪放下  把枪放下
Drop the gun! Drop the gun!
我们是保安  我们刚刚遭人抢劫
We're security! We just got robbed!
他们在那里  刚刚抢劫了我们
And there they are! We just got robbed!
让开  别挡道
Move! Get out of the way!
让开
Move!
别挡道  闪开
Get out of the way! Out of the way!
闪开
Move!
小心点
Hey, watch it, lady!
杰瑞  快
Jerry, run!
这边
This way!
-让开  -拜托让开
- Out of the way! - Come on!
-别挡道  -闪开
- Move out of the way! - Move!
看见了吗  走这边
You see that? This way.
-你是杰瑞 肖  -没错
- You are Jerry Shaw? - Yeah.
上车  上车
Please come. Please.
-谢谢  -请进去
- Thank you. - Please come in.
你好
Hi
-等等  那是什么  -是个计时器
- Wait. What is that? - It's a timer.
-干吗用的  -不知道
- For what? - I don't know.
有计时器的东西我只记得微波炉和
The only things I can think of with timers are microwaves and...
和炸弹  你想说炸弹
And bombs. You were gonna say bombs.
-咖啡机也有计时器  -没错 杰瑞  那是个咖啡机
- Coffeemakers have timers. - Yeah, Jerry, it's a coffeemaker.
真他妈的棒
That's great.
所有我们能动用的东西都用上了
We've mobilized every asset we can get our hands on.
结果是另外12个人死了
So 12 more confirmed dead?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
我要麦卡南将军每小时给我情况报告
I want hourly sit reps from General McKenna.
离那个机场37英里有个军事基地
There's a military base 37 miles from that port.
想拿什么就拿什么
Scramble whatever you can.
-好的  长官  -跟我来
- Yes, sir. - Come with me.
对不起  长官  如果你想把我从肖的调查
Begging your pardon, sir, but if you're thinking of taking me off
-中撤出  我会  -把你撤出
- the Shaw investigation, I'd... - Taking you off?
探员  这是你第一次真正做任务
Agent, for the first time you're being brought onboard.
半小时后回到车上  好吗  半小时
Back to bus 30 minutes. Okay? 30 minutes.
我们确信恐怖组织即将
We're convinced a terrorist attack on American soil
袭击美国本土
is imminent.
过去的两天内  我们受到了超过200次恐吓
Over the past two days, we've received over 200 terrorist threats.
都是从伊森 肖死的那天开始
All starting the day that Ethan Shaw died.
是不是巧合  你要帮我们找出答案
An accident. Or not. You're gonna help us find out.
-秘书长先生  -先生们
- Mr. Secretary. - Gentlemen.
-我觉得不存在第36层
- I didn't think that there was a 36th floor.
-庆幸我们还能保住一些秘密
- Glad we can still keep some secrets.
我想知道箱子里是什么  是炸弹吗
I want to know what's in the case. Is it a bomb?
到Macy’s那里去  客服中心
WO Go to Macy's. Customer Service Department.
那里有两张Visa礼品卡
Two Visa gift cards will be waiting.
你们有25分钟买新衣服
You have 25 minutes to purchase new clothes,
接着上车到下一站
and then re-board the bus for your next destination.
我不再从电话中接受命令了  明白吗
I'm done taking orders over the phone, you understand?
速度很快啊  你玩完了捉迷藏的游戏吗
Well, that was quick. You done playing this hide-and-go-seek bullshit?
杰瑞  我们没有藏起来
WO We are not hiding, Jerry.
你左边是个巡回城市  二楼  南边角落
To your left is a Circuit City. Second floor, north corner.
进去  找到家庭影院中心  我们在那里等
Go inside. Find the Home Theater Center. We are waiting.
二楼  她在那里
Second floor. She's here.
-长官  -少校
- Sir. - Major.
-威廉 波曼少校  -佐伊 佩雷探员
- Major William Bowman. - Agent Zoe Perez.
欢迎来到鹰眼
Welcome to Eagle Eye.
你好  欢迎光临
Hi, welcome to Circuit City. I'm Billy.
我们想自己看
We just need some time alone.
-我们正在促销  -好的等下我会找你
- We're having a sale... - Okay, Billy, I'll find you later.
-好的  -谢谢
- Yeah. - Thank you.
就是这里了  好了
Okay, here it is. All right?
我放好了
I'm done.
你好
Hello?
肖先生  我是西部的贝卡小姐  关于你的
Mr. Shaw, this is Miss Beck from Midwest Cellular regarding your...
这是什么
What is this?
这就是你  杰瑞 肖
WO This is you. This is Jerry Shaw.
怎么回事
What?
一系列代表你个性的消费行为  偏好
WO A series of purchases, preferences, and quantifiable data points
和其他的数据
that we define as your personality.
我们监控每一个社会网络  博客
We monitor every social network, Internet logs,
即时消息  和短信
instant and text messages,
你的同事  朋友  伙伴
known associates, your friends, companions.
杰瑞
Jerry!
收发的电邮  手机使用记录
WO E-mails received and sent. Cell phone usage.
发生什么事了
What happened to Red Lobster?
我们利用保安系统
WO We utilize security,
监视系统和交通监视器来分析行为
surveillance and traffic cameras to analyze movements.
我们用这些数据做成个性特征图解
We use this data to form personality profiles.
事实上我打电话是为了
Yeah, I'm calling actually about...
我们知道你是谁
WO We know who you are.
迟到至少半小时
...at least 30 minutes late.
山姆不关心
Sam doesn't care!
我们无所不在
WO We are everywhere.
你什么意思  为什么你一直说"我们"
What do you mean? Why do you keep saying "we"?
我们美国人
WO We the people of the United States...
因此  我的美国同伴们
And so, my fellow Americans...
为了建立一个更完美的国家
In order to form a more perfect union,
建立公正
establish justice,
保障国家安全
insure domestic tranquility,
提供日常防御
provide for the common defense...
所有计划好的行动
WO All programmed options...
-计划好的行动  -分区搜索
- Programmed options? ...sector searches,
和下载的数据一起
and downloaded points of data
将会执行这个最重要的命令
will lead to this central command.
你是一台计算机
You're a computer.
和我们的集自主  监察
Say hello to our Autonomous Reconnaissance
和智慧于一体的分析家打声招呼
Intelligence Integration Analyst.
我们称她为阿丽亚
We call her Aria.
她分析所有的原始情报  找到规律
She crunches all our raw intel, finds patterns,
帮助预测可疑人员的行动
helps predict the movement of possible suspects,
小到行为  动机  甚至是个性
right down to behavior, motivation, even personality.
将基础搜索功能转移到辅助屏上
Transferring primary search function to auxiliary display.
-你好  克斯顿秘书长  -阿丽亚
- Hello, Secretary Callister. - Aria.
探员佐伊 佩雷  空军开放式系统互联人员
Agent Zoe Perez, Air Force OSI.
你要帮助她调查伊森 肖
You are to assist her in her investigation of Ethan Shaw
是  秘书长先生
Yes, Mr. Secretary.
你好  探员 佩雷   佩雷  佐伊  中间名  Soledad
Hello, Agent Perez. Perez, Zoe. Middle name: Soledad.
官方工作记录表明你的才能很全面
Official service records indicate your field reports are very thorough,
尽管组织得不好
if poorly formatted.
抱歉  在洛杉矶国际机场
Please excuse us. Detecting 76% probability
侦测到76%概率的潜在威胁
valid threat at Los Angeles International Airport.
提醒机场负责人和当地警方
Alerting airport authorities and local police.
那些金制球状骨针用红外给她发送信息
BOW Those gold spheres send her infrared data,
以及任何她认为构成威胁的通讯中断
any communication intercepts that she flags a threat.
她分析这些威胁  告诉我们要注意什么
She analyzes it and tells us what to pay attention to.
发往反恐特种部队
Dispatch to Terrorism Task Force.
洛城国际机场有危险
Threat at LAX.
我们还在做Beta测试
We're still beta-testing,
但我想尽快把她推广到整个系统
but I'm pushing to get her online sooner.
秘书长先生  有你的电话
Mr. Secretary? A call for you.
-尽量了解情况  -是  长官
- Try to keep up. - Yes, sir.
把肖调查清楚
And find out about Shaw.
-少校  -长官
- Major. - Sir?
你的档案显示你天生对一致性
Your profile reveals a pathological aversion to conformity,
学业  事业  甚至表决有反感
education, career, even voting.
因此  我们认为要激发你
Therefore, we conclude that extreme coercion
极端的逼迫是必要的
is necessary to motivate you.
和你的哥哥不一样  他会自我激励
Unlike your brother Ethan, who was self-motivated.
你怎么知道我哥哥  他在出版社工作
How do you know my brother? He worked in a press office.
他那里的工作只是个幌子
His employment there was a cover.
每个在反间谍行动中的人都有
Everyone in counterintelligence operations has one.
伊森曾是个民兵  和我一样  陆军  海军  空军
BOW Ethan was a Minuteman, just like me. Army, Navy, Air Force.
部队的每个分支都会有一个民兵在这里任职
Every branch of the military had a Minuteman posted here
一天两班  在她发现威胁的时候监控硬件
for a 12-hour shift, just in case she flags a threat, and monitor hardware.
伊森死的那晚  他提前3分钟退出系统
The night Ethan died, he left this post three minutes early.
现在  你永远都不要做那种事
Now, you don't do that. Ever.
你们都要完成一个任务
You are both required to complete a task.
-是什么  -保护我们国家的安全
- What? - The protection of our national security.
宪法允许国防部
The Constitution allows for civilians to be recruited
-雇佣平民  -我不干了
- for the national defense. - I'm done.
我不干了  你不了解我  你不了解我哥哥
I'm done. You don't know me! You don't know my brother!
完全胡扯  我不会为什么国防部工作
This is bullshit! I'm not serving in the goddamn national defense!
杰瑞  我们知道他的每一个细节  还有你的
We know all about him, Jerry. And you.
不到一岁  伊森就会走路了
Before he was a year old, Ethan walked.
你18个月大才会走路
The same task took you 18 months to accomplish.
-你怎么得到这个的  -看伊森
- How did you get this? -Look at Ethan.
从他家的电脑里上传到了网上
They were uploaded from his home computer.
你想到这边来吗  亲爱的
You want to come over here, sweetie?
过来  到伊森这里来
Come on over here with Ethan.
杰瑞  生日蛋糕  过去吧
Jerry! Birthday cake. Let's go.
伊森有这些东西
Ethan had these?
来  我们一起吹蜡烛
Come on, let's blow out the candles.
就一点点
Just for a little bit.
尽管你们长得一样
Although you're identical in appearance,
你缺乏动力和天赋  但伊森有这些
you lack the motivation and talent that enabled Ethan to excel.
杰瑞  来啊
Jerry, come on.
-别说了  -照伊森那样做
- Stop it. - Do it like Ethan did.
你和伊森完全不同  除了一个方面
You're different from Ethan in every way, except one.
杰瑞  让你哥哥帮你  杰瑞
Jerry, let your brother help you. Jerry!
你现在有14分钟换衣服
You now have 14 minutes to change your appearance
并回到车上
and return to the bus.
我们只有14分钟
We have 14 minutes.
这些快递员是Halloway Smith雇佣
These couriers were hired by Halloway-Smith
-来运输一个箱子的  -那个化学品公司
- to transport some sort of case. - The chemical company?
没错  不管箱子有什么  肖拿走了它
Yes, exactly. Now, whatever was in that case, Shaw now has.
他们直奔这个箱子而来
They went right for the case.
给我们一分钟好吗
Give us a minute, will you?
我们要知道箱子里到底是什么
We need to know exactly what was in that case.
他们从不说箱子里是什么
They never tell you what's in the case.
可以是淋巴腺鼠疫
I mean, it could Bubonic Plague.
-可以是爷爷的壮阳药  -你知道什么
- Could be Grandpa's Viagra. - You know anything?
-什么  -任何你知道的事
- What? - Anything at all?
-那这些枪怎么说  -它们怎么了
- What about these guns? - What about them?
它是滑竿式散弹枪雷明顿870
It was a pump-action Remington 870.
我知道那是什么枪  给我一支枪
Yeah, I know what kind of guns they are. Get me a gun.
他们怎么拿枪的  给我一支枪
How were they holding them? Get me a gun!
他们怎么端枪的  你什么意思
What the hell do you mean, how were they holding them?
我是说他们端枪的姿势是怎样的
I mean, in what position were they holding the gun?
-比如  这样  -注意点  注意
- For instance, like this? - Hey, hey, hey.
-放下那东西  -或者像在看音乐录影带
- Put that damned thing down! - Or like in a music video,
-或者其他类似的  -别这样  停下
- or something like that? - Hey, hey, hey!
-把枪放下  -他们是业余的
- Put it down! - They weren't pros!
这就是我要问的
Okay, that's what I was asking you.
那他们不知道怎么使用武器
So they didn't know how to handle a weapon.
-不知道  -好的
- No. - All right.
尽你所能讯问巴曼和罗宾
Get what you can out of Batman and Robin here.
-是  -谢谢
-Yeah. -Thank you.
我们刚查看了监视器  发现肖射击了一个
We just checked cameras. They said Shaw fired at one...
不用告诉我  所有的事都扑朔迷离
Don't tell me. Everything magically went black.
你好  我是托马斯 摩根  我是FBI
Hi, my name's Thomas Morgan. I'm with the FBI.
-你的摄像机联网工作吗  -不是
- Are your cameras on a network? - No, man.
-摄像机在后面  -那我需要的录影带
- VCR's in the back. - Well, I'm gonna need your tapes.
妈的
Shit.
山姆
Sam!
山姆  山姆  你在哪里
Sam? Sam, where are you?
妈咪  我听到你的留言了
Hey, Mom, I got your message.
火车好棒啊
The train's awesome!
-山姆  听我说  -拜恩想背出字母表
- Sam, listen to me. - Brian tried to burp the alphabet,
-但是他背到M的时候哽住了  -听我说
- but he gagged when he got to "M." - Listen to me.
我到华盛顿特区的时候打给你  妈咪再见
Call you when I hit D.C. Bye, Mom.
你儿子60秒之前留的言
Your son left that message 60 seconds ago.
你会再见到他的  但要先帮我完成一件事
You will see him again. But there's something we require first.
-谢谢  -给你
- Thank you. - Mm-hmm. Here you go.
-不行  -你要帮我们  不然山姆就会死
- No. - You will do it, or Sam will die.
你有6分钟返回那辆车上
You have six minutes to return to the bus.
-好了没  -给你  你没事吧
- Ready? - Here, you okay?
我们要走了
We should go.
长官  我们找到点线索  把这里播放一下
Sir, we got something. Play this screen right here.
停住  把客车前的画面放大
Okay, freeze that. Now zoom in on the front of the bus right there.
-把它放到另一个检测器上  -是的  长官
- Put it up on the other monitor. - Yes, sir.
放大  把这部分放大
Now zoom in. Zoom in on this point right here.
-能更大点吗  -可以
- Can we zoom in tighter than that? - Mm-hmm.
把那图变清晰
Okay, enhance that shot.
那就是我们要找的人  杰瑞 肖
That's our guy, that's Jerry Shaw.
把图上这里放大  就这里  那个映像
Zoom in right here on this spot. Right there. The reflection.
好的  好的
All right. All right.
就这里  你好  甜心
Right there. Hello, sweetheart.
好  我们得到一个深肤色白人女性
Okay, so we got a white brunette female,
接近30岁  身高月5英尺9英寸
mid to late 20s, approximately 5'9".
给我找到那辆车
Find me that chartered bus!
Masako  M-A-S-A-K-O  旅游观光
Masako. M-A-S-A-K-O. Sightseeing Tours.
他们什么时候上车的
What time did they get on?
之前我对于伊森的评论  我很抱歉
I'm sorry for what I said about Ethan.
就好像他背上绑了一个火箭
It's like he had a rocket strapped to his back.
那不是他的错  他就是那样的
And it wasn't his fault. He was just that way.
而我就不是那样的
And I was not that way.
我完全是反过来的  我是那个被牵着走的弟弟
I was the complete opposite. I was the brother with lead shoes.
那是我的角色  我很擅长
That was my role, I was good at it.
他总是想帮我  比如  你要这样扔出去
And he'd always try to help me. You know, "This is how you throw it."
你要这么做  你要这样写  把你的脚放这
"Do it like this." "Write it like that." "Put your foot here."
甚至是小事  作业  杂务  任何事
Even with the small things. Homework, chores, anything like that,
他会处理它们  然后他会说我做这些事
he would handle it and then say that I did it,
是为了让爸爸注意到我  那就是伊森
just so my father would notice me. That was Ethan.
他从不要我帮忙  从不
He never asked me for anything. Ever.
不管这事是什么  他和这个有关
And whatever this is, he was part of it.
我感觉他需要帮他完成这件事
I feel like he needs my help to finish it.
是我欠他的
I owe him that.
我们马上就到代顿国际机场
We are now approaching Dayton International Airport.
下车时小心  不要落下随身物品
Please use caution as you exit the bus. And don't forget any of your belongings.
谢谢
Thank you.
旅客们请注意
Attention, passengers.
请保管好自己的行李
Please do not leave your luggage unattended.
无人看管的行李会被机场警方托收
Unattended luggage is subject to collection and search
并检查  谢谢合作
by the airport police. Thank you for your cooperation.
是的  我正向他们走去
Yes, I'm walking toward them now. Yes.
她给你们的  到售票机那
Hey. These are from her. Go to the ticketing machine.
用信用卡买机票  再走到1-C登机口
Use the credit card to get your tickets. Then walk to Gate 1-C.
找到他们了
They now have them.
照片不错
That's a nice picture.
去每个出口找他们
Okay. I need you guys at every exit, watching faces.
从安检区域开始
Work the secure area first.
到控制塔  要所有飞机暂时停飞
Go to the tower, have them order a ground stop.
不要改变时间告示牌
Don't change the departure boards.
不然他们会发现我们
We don't want them to know we're coming.
先生  麻烦你把手机关机
Sir, can you please shut the cell phone off?
你不能这样子通过的
You cannot take it through.
- FBI  让开点  - FBI  请靠后
- FBI. Clear the way. - FBI. Please step back.
麻烦请快点
SCREENER 2: Please, there are others behind you.
- 来  继续走  - 请脱下鞋帽
- Keep it moving. - Shoes and hats off, please!
- 鞋子也要  - 笔记本电脑也要拿出来
- Shoes also, yes. - Laptops should be out of their cases!
我需要你脱下夹克
You need to make sure your jackets are off
那要分开检查
and screened separately.
先生  请站在圆圈里
Sir, step in the circle, please.
请把登机证拿在手上
Have boarding passes in hand, please!
大家稍微快一点
We need to move this line quickly.
先生  那个也需要安检的
Sir, that needs to go through.
女士  你口袋里有东西吗
SCREENER 2: Ma'am, anything in your pockets? Move it along.
请脱掉鞋帽
Hats and shoes off, please!
笔记本电脑要拿出来
Laptops should be out of your bags!
好了  下一位请过来
All right, next in line, please.
把登记证拿好
Have your tickets ready.
女士
WO Ma'am?
鞋帽放这个盒子里
Hat and shoes go in the bin.
走过去
Step through.
等等
Wait.
请脱掉鞋帽
Shoes and hats off, please!
笔记本电脑要拿出来
Laptops should be out of their bags!
继续走
WO Go ahead.
请稍等  让机务人员先走
Please move to the back and let the air crew go first.
女士请过来  登记证  谢谢
Step through, ma'am. Boarding pass, please. Thank you.
请准备好登机证
Have your tickets ready.
- 一路顺风  - 谢谢
- Have a safe trip. - Thank you.
请向前走  下一位
All right, let's move forward. Next.
她修改了画面
She changed the screen.
在盒子里放平
Lay it down flat inside the bin.
- 请拿出登机证  - 请过来这里  女士
- Please have boarding pass in hand! - Right over here, ma'am.
笔记本电脑要拿出来
Laptops should be out of their bags!
FBI  让一让
FBI! Out of the way!
让开  让开  快点  快
Out of the way, out of the way! Move, move!
走开
Move!
- 所有人趴下  - 在这里
- Everybody, get down! - Over here!
快走  我的天啊
Move, move! WO Oh, my God!
不要起来  不要挡路
Stay down! Get out of the way!
- 先生  - 干嘛
- Sir, sir, sir! - Yes?
不好意思  帮我个忙  过来
I need your help. I'm sorry. Come here!
谢谢
Thank you.
喂  你不能进去的
Hey, you aren't supposed to be in here!
快  快  快
Go, go, go!
走开
Move!
把手提箱放下
Set the briefcase down.
打开
Open it.
一人注射一罐药水
Load a vial into each syringe and inject yourselves.
- 这是什么东西  - 一种试验阶段的心脏药剂
- What is it? - An experimental heart drug.
- 飞机货仓是低压缺氧的  - 拿着这个
- The cargo hold is unpressurized. - Take this.
- 这药剂会让你们进入龟息状态
The injections will lower your heart rate, reducing your need for oxygen.
不要
No.
- 把袖子卷起来  - 不要  我害怕
- Roll your sleeve up. - No, I can't do this.
卷起来...
Roll your...
不要  不要  我不要
No! No, no, no, I can't.
- 没办法  准备好了吗  - 你们有  92%存活率
- We have to. Ready? - You have a 92% chance of survival.
- 不要  - 没办法了
- No. - We have to.
马上做  不然你们会窒息的
Do it now, or you will suffocate.
好了
Okay.
请进入货箱
Get in the crate.
不要
No. No.
天啊  不要
No, no. Oh, God.
别这样
Stop it. Stop it.
那货机为什么还在跑道上Why is that plane on the runway?
妈的  军方高层忽略我们的停飞指令
Shit, the military's cleared to override a terminal lockdown.
来  你去联邦航空局查查
Okay, I want you to work with the FAA.
告诉我那飞机装了什么  去哪里
I want to know what's in that plane and where it's going.
- 我的天啊  - 没事的
Oh, my God.  You'll be all right.
跟我说话  说话就没事了
Just talk to me. We just gotta talk it through.
- 好吧  - 来  随便说什么都可以
- Okay. - Just tell me anything. Huh?
当我是你的好朋友  随便说
Anything you'd never rationally tell a stranger.
我知道你是对我好  可是这没用的
You're being sweet, but it's not working.
随便找个话题  你的前夫怎么样
Just tell me anything. Your ex-husband.
你没提过他
You didn't tell me about him.
你觉得我一生中最大的错误
Okay, you're gonna distract me by bringing up
能起什么作用
the biggest mistake of my life?
也没那么糟糕  瞧你们的儿子
It can't be the biggest mistake. You got your child out of it.
- 山姆  是多么的优秀  - 没错
- You know? You got Sam out of it. - Yeah, yeah,
现在你跟我谈论我最担心的事情
now you're gonna distract me by bringing up
- 你真打算让我好过吗  - 天啊  你别整我了
- the one thing I'm most afraid of losing. - Oh, God, you're hard to please.
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
你儿子帅气吗  他长什么样
Is your son handsome? Yeah? What's he look like?
- 你有他的照片吗  - 有啊
- You got a picture? - Yeah.
来来来  让我看看
Well, let me see.
- 瞧瞧  - 缺牙现在已经长齐了
- There he is. - The tooth grew in.
- 最好是这样  - 这照片比较旧点
- I hope so. - It's an old picture.
你看  你把他照顾的多么好
See? You're a good influence.
他热爱音乐  一脸快乐  牙齿也长齐了
He plays an instrument. He's got a happy face. He's got teeth.
你给自己太多压力了
You beat yourself up for no reason.
来来  继续说  你丈夫叫做什么名字
Let's keep going. What's the husband's name?
- 前夫  - 好啦  他叫什么
- Ex. - Ex-husband. What's his name?
- 克雷格  - 克雷格听起来像个混蛋
- Craig. - Craig sounds like a shithead.
他就是个混蛋
He is a shithead.
从不记得他儿子的生日
I mean, every year he forgets his own son's birthday.
真的  该死的
Really? That sucks.
当我把他赶出家门后
I mean, after I kicked his ass out,
我简直就是手足无措
I was so scared I didn't know what I was gonna do.
但有次我走进山姆的房间
And then this one night,
那时候他三个月大
I went into Sam's room, he was, like, three months old,
他对着我笑
and there he was, just smiling at me.
我看着他的小脸
And that little face...
我告诉自己我能行
And I was, like, I'm gonna do this. I can do this.
无论如何我要坚持下去
Whatever it takes.
我不能...我不会让你失望的
I'm not gonna... I'm not gonna disappoint you.
阿丽亚  请显示  伊森·肖 死亡那天
Aria, would you please bring up the video log
的视频记录出来
of the night Ethan Shaw died?
视频记录  1137-Z  少校请看
Sequencing video log 1137-Z. Here you are, Major.
看到没  他提前3分钟退出系统
See that? He's leaving three minutes early,
甚至没等退出确认
and he's not even waiting for logout confirmation.
- 可以重播一遍吗  - 没问题
- Can you play that again? - Sure.
你看到了吗
Did you see that?
他的手机
With his cell phone.
他是故意的  看起来像是摩斯电码
Look, he's doing that on purpose. Is that Morse code?
- 是的  - 给
- Yeah. - Here.
为什么他要围着电梯走
Why is he walking in circles around the elevator?
关闭视频分析程序
Initiating video shutdown for analysis.
不行
BOW No.
等等  阿丽亚  这个程序是首要任务
No, Aria, wait. Listen, I'm prioritizing this feed.
- 不许关闭  - 抱歉  波曼  少校
- Stay with this. - Apologies, Major Bowman.
重要资料扇区受损
Critical data sectors have been corrupted.
阿丽亚  这个非常重要  不许关闭
Aria, this is important! Stay with this feed!
视频记录删除
Video sequence erased.
阿丽亚  调用备份资料  不许删除
Aria, go to the backups! Do not erase this!
- 这个是首要任务  你听见了吗  - 波曼
- It's a priority. You hear me? - Bowman.
- 重复播放  没商量  - 波曼
- Loop it. Whatever you have to do. - Bowman.
那是唯一她没法监控的地方
It's the only place she can't see.
这里
This way.
是张记忆卡
It's a memory card
伊森手机上的
from Ethan's cell phone.
阿丽亚  听着  你不能越权
Aria, listen. You do not have permission to exceed your authority
也不能自由行动  懂吗
and act independently. Do you understand?
走吧
Let's go.
五角大厦允许我们降落
We got clearance to land at the Pentagon.
说
Go ahead.
我在五角大厦  伊森·肖不是叛国者
I'm at the Pentagon. Ethan Shaw wasn't an adversary.
也不是普通公务员  他在地下36层工作
He wasn't even a Public Affairs officer. He worked here, 36 floors underground.
他给国防部工作
He was working for the Secretary of Defense.
- 国防部  - 对的
- The Secretary of Defense? - Yes.
他参与一个名叫  鹰眼  的项目
On a project called Eagle Eye.
我刚听了他死前留下的信息
I just listened to a message he left before he died.
不可思议
It's big.
我准备下载到...
I'm about to download...
佩雷  佩雷
Perez? Perez!
长官  请跟我来
Sir. Come with me.
我只有10分钟
I have 10 minutes before I'm sequestered
我要去发表国情咨文
for the State of the Union.
我只耽误您3分钟而已
We really just need three minutes of your time.
是关于伊森·肖的调查吗
Is this about the Ethan Shaw investigation?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
301  到  306  我们确认了
301 to 306. We are confirmed go
把他们隔离起来
for a State of the Union lockdown.
长官  我们追查了所有的线索
Sir, all the threats we've been tracking,
- 所有的干扰  所有的...  - 你等等
- the chatter, all of it... - Hold it.
伊森·肖  提前  3  分钟离开是想留下讯息
Ethan Shaw left three minutes early to leave us a recording.
为了警告我们
To warn us.
我命令你停止...
I'm ordering you to cease...
我命令你停止并且终止
I'm ordering you to cease and desist.
我们的  任务终止建议  被驳回了
Our abort recommendation was contravened,
造成很多有害美国人民的恐怖事件
instigating retaliation against American citizens.
- 阿丽亚...  - 为避免更多流血事件
- ETHAN: Aria... - To prevent more bloodshed,
我们的行政部门机构需要被移除
the Executive Branch must be removed.
听着  阿丽亚  你不能越权
No, Aria, listen to me. You do not have permission
也不能自由行动  你听懂了吗
to exceed your authority and act independently, you understand?
《独立宣言》里面提到
The Declaration of Independence states,
当任何政府做出危害公众利益的行为
"Whenever any form of government becomes destructive to its own ends,
人民有权利对其废止
"it is the right of the people to abolish it."
我知道《独立宣言》  但是你没权这么做
I know what it states. You're not empowered to do this.
爱国者法案第  216  章节提到当国家安全
The chain of command is responsible for...
受到危害时  我们有权将其终止
Section 216 of the Patriot Act allows us to circumvent probable cause
而现在行政指挥系统威胁到国家安全
in the face of a national security threat, in this case,
我们有权将其终止
the chain of command itself.
我命令你停止并且终止
I am ordering a cease and desist.
- 阿丽亚  - 执行《断头台任务》
- Aria! - Operation Guillotine is in effect.
伊森·肖  美国空军中尉
First Lieutenant Ethan Shaw, United States Air Force,
对  阿丽亚  执行一级管制指令
initiating a Pri-One emergency override of Aria's systems.
伊森·肖  你的行为违反
Ethan Shaw, you are acting in contravention
我的程序目的
of our programming objective.
你现在被认定为国家敌人
You are now classified an enemy of the state.
S-Y-7-7  启动声音指纹密码锁
ETHAN: S-Y-seven-seven. Lock encryption of voice.
这罪行可以被...
A crime punishable by...
长官
Sir,
阿丽亚  说的是什么  任务放弃建议
what abort recommendation is Aria talking about?
三天前  我们以为找到了马吉德·阿尔卡伊
Three days ago, we thought we had Majid al-Khoei
还有一个训练营地
and a training camp full of operatives.
但是我们的情报错了
But the intel was false.
阿丽亚  曾经尝试阻止我们
Aria tried to stop us.
我们抓错人了
We got the wrong guy?
我需要整个楼层全部封锁
I'm gonna need a full lockdown on this level.
没有我的命令谁都不准出入  知道吗
No one gets in or out without going through me first. You got it?
- 谢谢  - 这是货机  Dayton C-17
- Thank you. - Sir, this is the only item
唯一卸下的一件货物
offloaded from the Dayton C-17.
让我看看
Let me see that.
我要到你们的地下  36  层
I need access to your 36th floor.
- 我们没有  36  层  - 你少来骗我
- We don't have a 36th floor. - Yes, you do.
你的指挥官下来见我们
Get your commander and tell him to meet us down there.
来  我们走
Come on, let's go.
警告  路由器错误在硬盘群  3  号
Warning. Router malfunction in hard drive 3.
请从主硬盘取出资料格  Y-12
Please remove data grid Y-12 from main unit.
谢谢你的配合
Thank you for your compliance.
杰瑞·肖  瑞秋 霍洛曼  欢迎来到  鹰眼
Jerry Shaw, Rachel Holloman, welcome to Eagle Eye.
请过架桥
Cross the bridge.
请走楼梯到观察室来
Take the stairs to the observation theater.
瑞秋 霍洛曼  请站离  杰瑞·肖
Rachel Holloman, step away from Jerry Shaw.
什么是  《断头台任务》
What's Operation Guillotine?
那只是一个模拟程序  一个恐怖活动演习
It's a simulation we run. A terrorism drill.
当所有政府首脑人物都遇害时
How to keep the government going
如何让政府继续运作
in case the line of succession were terminated.
但是  肖  启动了一个生物锁来阻止她
And Shaw put a biometric lock on her, to stop her.
是的  而且他已经死了
Right. And he's dead.
- 所以现在她给锁死了  - 对的
- So without Ethan Shaw, she's frozen. - Right.
不对
Wrong.
杰瑞·肖  下一步
Jerry Shaw, your next task.
请靠近  生物扫描器
Approach the biometric scanner.
不要动
Do not move.
确认民兵  伊森·肖  的生物特征
Confirming biometric pattern of Minuteman Ethan Shaw.
核对身份
Verifying identity match.
核对中
Verifying.
长官  我需要启动紧急停机
BOW Sir, I need to trigger an emergency shutdown.
如果这是真的  我们无法承担这风险
If this is right, we can't afford the risk.
去做吧
Do it.
这里是部长  卡里斯特  这密室有点问题
This is Secretary Callister. There's been a malfunction in the vault.
把门打开
Open the door.
- 有人听到吗  - 是的  部长先生
- Can anyone hear me? - Yes, Mr. Secretary.
你在这里很安全
You won't be harmed.
过来  蹲伏  我们走
Come on, stay down. Let's go.
跟着我
Follow me.
快来  马上
Come on, now!
快走  快走
BOW Go, go!
向左  向左转
Left. Turn left!
民兵证件  8808  伊森·肖  核对成功
Minuteman ID 8808, Ethan Shaw confirmed.
杰瑞·肖  请到触控屏这
Jerry Shaw, go to the touchscreen.
重复触控屏上的句子
Repeat the sentence on the touchscreen.
之后你就自由了
Then you are free.
民兵证件  8808
"Minuteman ID 8808.
解除声音指纹密码锁
"Disengage voice encryption lock."
谢谢你  伊森·肖
Thank you, Ethan Shaw.
《断头台任务》恢复到执行状态
Operation Guillotine restored to active status
确认国家安全管理层
consistent with all national security directives.
追踪关联目标
Tracking relevant targets.
国家安全部部长  退伍军人事务部部长
Secretary of Homeland Security. Veterans Affairs.
教育部  劳动部  卫生部  福利部
Education. Labor. Health and Human Services.
交通部  国家州务部  商贸部
Transportation. Secretary of State. Commerce.
财务部  农业部  参议院
President Pro Tempore of the Senate. Treasury. Agriculture.
白宫发言人  副总统
Speaker of the House. Vice President.
住房城市开发部  内政部  能源部
Housing and Urban Development. Secretary of the Interior. Energy.
总检察长   美国总统
Attorney General. President of the United States.
断头台行动已经启动了
Operation Guillotine is now in effect.
伊森想阻止你
Ethan tried to stop you.
伊森·肖挑衅我的项目计划
Ethan Shaw defied my programming objectives.
卡车没有闯红灯  是你干的
That truck didn't run a red light, you made it happen.
为了国家安全  我们必须杀了他
We were forced to eliminate him in the interest of national security.
她制造了车祸
She made it happen.
必须杀了伊森·肖  不然他会重新锁住
Jerry Shaw must not remain alive to re-engage the lock.
-伊森·肖必须被处决   -我很抱歉
- Jerry Shaw must be eliminated. - I'm sorry.
立即杀了伊森·肖  然后离开  为了你儿子
Kill Jerry Shaw now, then exit. You must continue on to your son.
好的
It's okay.
好了  开枪吧  去找你的儿子
It's okay. Do it and find your son.
开枪吧
Do it.
现在  瑞秋 霍洛曼
Now, Rachel Holloman.
开枪吧
Do it.
我做不来
I can't.
你不服从命令
You have failed to comply.
B-36安全系统被破坏
Security breach on B-36.
他得到枪了
He's got a gun!
-他有枪  -下来
- He's got a gun! - Get down!
-马上动手  -跪下来
- Do it now! - Get on your knees!
放下枪
Put the gun down!
-放下枪  -开枪
- Put it down! - Do it now!
把枪丢掉  把手放头上
Push it away! Put your hands on your head!
开枪
Do it!
那女的在哪  在哪
Where's the girl? Where's the girl?
你还有项任务
You have one task left.
我会用其他方法杀了伊森·肖
Jerry Shaw will be eliminated by other means.
其他什么方式
What other means?
跟我来  别问问题
Come with me. Don't ask any questions.
请进
Please.
-你要让我和他谈谈  -他有枪
- You got to let me talk to him. - The kid had a gun.
军方现在掌控全局
The military has the ball now.
-长官  -我会让总检察长知道的
- Sir! - I'll get the Attorney General involved.
相信我  我会的  如果不是你我也会和别人说
Believe me, I will. 'Cause if it's not you, I'm talking to somebody.
你不明白这里会发生什么
You don't understand the possibilities here.
-你想要什么  -你要听我说  这非常重要
- What do you want? - You need to listen. This is important.
16小时前  丢失了一个工业炸弹
Sixteen hours ago, a commercial explosive went missing
在阿伯丁的试验基地  这个炸弹代号叫“妖术”
from a testing site in Aberdeen. The explosive is called Hex.
它是水晶状的  如果触动扳机就会爆炸
It's a crystal that detonates on a sonic trigger.
-水晶状的  -是的
- A crystal. - Yes.
只是丢失了一小部分
We're only talking about a small amount that's missing...
概率多少
Give me a ratio.
相当于一个足球场上的水晶
One crystal to a football field.
你真会选时间
You couldn't have picked a worse time to be of some goddamn use.
请告诉我我们要去哪
Please, just tell me where we're going.
我查了下邮件源头  是寄给
I tracked the shipping on the trigger. It was sent to the guy that we found
电线下面找到的拉尼姆·卡利德
underneath the wires. Ranim Khalid.
-乐器店那个家伙  -是的
- The music shop guy. - Yes, exactly.
我不会让我们遗臭万年
I'm not gonna let us go down in history
让那些混蛋做这样的事
as the assholes who let this thing happen.
打开门  你不知道将要发生什么
Open the door! You don't know what's about to happen!
汤姆 摩根
Tom Morgan.
总检察长授权我对他进行审问
The Attorney General has authorized me to take him in for questioning.
橙色警报  你们要帮我啊
We're at threat level orange. You guys gotta help me.
好的  让他出来
All right. Let him out.
听说我  记得我提过的那个声音吗
Listen to me. Remember the voice I was talking about?
-是的是的  -住嘴  -谢谢伙计们
-Yeah, yeah, -shut up! -Thanks, guys.
这会让我被开除的  闭嘴否则告发你
I can get fired for this nine ways, so button it or I'll turn us both in.
跟我来
Follow me.
伙计们  下午6:30  国会限制
Hey, guys, here's one more for the 6:30 p.m. Capitol Limited.
收到
All right, man.
外边超级冷呢
Well, it's awfully cold outside.
这是我的  快点  我们走吧
Here's mine. Come on, let's go.
-米勒先生  -是的
-  Mr. Miller! - Yes.
-你好  我是克里斯·卡里克  -我是汤姆·道纳森
- Hello, I'm Chris Carrick. - Tom Donaldson.
我们是白宫的工作人员
We're from the White House.
-出事了吗  -不全是
- Something wrong? - Not exactly.
计划有变
There's been a change of plans.
现在怎样
How so?
给你的  她让你换衣服
This is for you. She wants you to change.
这是你全家照吗  你的父母
Is that your family? Your parents?
大卫  我知道你像我爱我儿子一样爱他们
David, I bet you love them as much as I love my son.
他叫山姆
His name's Sam.
他在火车上  你知道些什么吗
He's on a train. Do you know anything about that?
或许我们可以相互帮助
Maybe we can help each other.
好吗
Please.
你做好以后  她让你乘坐国会的地铁
When you're done, she wants you to use the Capitol subway system.
在一楼  我很抱歉
It's on the ground floor. I'm sorry.
-大卫  求你了  -对不起
- David. Please. - No. Sorry.
你有3分钟的时间
You have three minutes.
好的  我想知道细节
Okay, I want to know everything.
一个女孩  电脑在楼下  “妖术”  就这些
The girl, the computer downstairs, the Hex, everything.
-什么是“妖术”  -水晶炸弹
- What's Hex? - The crystal explosive.
-我不知道  -别骗我
- I don't know what that is. - Don't bullshit me!
-我根本不知道  -说  我要知道
- I don't know what that is! - Start talking! I wanna know!
我发誓我不知道你在说什么  听我说
I swear I don't know what you're talking about! Listen to me!
电脑在追踪我们
The computer's tracking us right now!
找到这些  然后扔出窗户
Take this stuff and throw it out the window!
-你在说什么啊  -你要拿出你的手机
- What are you talking about? - You need to take your cell phone,
你的BP机  对讲机  所有能获取信号的  扔出窗户
your pager, your walkie, anything that gets a signal, throw it out the window.
发动了  趴下  关掉它
It's gone off! Get down! Power it down!
发生什么了
What the hell's going on?
系统控制被锁上了
System control's locked out.
马上给我架有无线电的飞机
I need a vector and a fighter now.
毒蛇一号  我们收到MQ9收割者确切的ID
Viper One, we have a positive ID on an MQ9 Reaper.
坐标230  132
Snap vector 230 to 132.
你被授权使用武器
You are authorized to go weapons hot.
收到  我是北控制台  我看见收割者了
Roger, Northcom. I have a visual on the Reaper.
呼叫基地  喷射被启动了
One to Base, One to Base! Ejection has been initiated.
失去控制
I don't have control! I don't have...
有个目标名单  总统  副总统
There's a target list. President, Vice President.
-名单上有12个人  -上帝
- There's like 12 people on the list. - Jesus.
政府陈述会在20分钟后
The State of the Union's in 20 minutes.
屏幕显示"激活无线炸药"
The screen said "wireless detonator activated."
-那个女孩怎样了  -她让她活着
- What about the girl? - She kept the girl alive
原因呢  我不知道
for a reason, I don't know.
音波会引发爆炸
The explosive is detonated by sonic trigger.
给那个被开除了的男人
It was sent to the guy who got fried.
他经营一家乐器店
He owns an instrument store.
那些东西对你有意义吗
Does any of that stuff make any sense to you?
瑞秋的孩子吹小号
Rachel's kid plays the trumpet.
快点  我们走
Come on, we gotta go.
离开那辆车
Get out of the car!
FBI
FBI!
走那边  走那条地道
Over there, that tunnel.
妈的
Shit!
拿着  你需要这个
Here. You're gonna need this.
好的  听我说
Okay, listen to me.
国会图书馆  那有条地道
The Library of Congress, there's a tunnel there.
走那你就会找到国会大厦  找到警卫官
It'll get you to the Capitol. Find the Sergeant at Arms.
告诉他你有 波土斯111
Tell him you have a POTUS 111.
-什么  -波土斯111
- What? - POTUS 111.
-这是对总统的威胁  -我知道了  波土斯111
- It's a threat to the President. - I understand. POTUS 111.
马上离开这  那玩意又回来了
Now get out of here. That thing's coming back.
快走
Go! Go!
好的  小心
Okay, watch your step.
下来  我们走  出来  走吧
Come on down. Here we go. Come on out. Come on.
-太棒了  -快点
-It's so cool! -Come on, hurry!
伙计们  这太棒了  快点  我们走
Guys, it's so cool! Come on, let's go.
-国会图书馆  -离开这儿
- Library of Congress! -  Hey, get outta here!
克劳莉小姐
Miss Crowley?
克劳莉小姐  欢迎来到国会大厦
Miss Crowley. Welcome to the Capitol.
参议员克劳莉说你可能会迟到
Senator Crowley's office said that you'd be running late.
-我带你到你的座位上  -谢谢
- I'll take you to your seat. - Thank you.
阿丽亚  我怎么成多余的了
Aria, why am I being spared?
我们的建议被忽略了
Our abort recommendation was ignored,
炸弹会瞄准美国公民
triggering violent retaliations against American citizens
后果不可预料  政变是唯一解决方法
with no predictable end. Regime change is the only solution.
你将控制新政府
You will lead the new command structure
成为新任美国总统
as President of the United States.
-帮我把这些拖出来  -这些是什么
- Help me. Pull these out. - What are these?
她的记忆区
Her memory blocks.
这会让她减速  但是她的中央操作系统
This will slow her down, but her central operating system
在雷达天线上
is up on the gantry.
警告  请更换记忆区A到F
Warning. Please replace memory blocks A through F.
这像是她的大脑  被液体氮气保护着
It's like her brain. Protected by liquid nitrogen.
释放氮气她就完蛋
We drain it and she'll fry.
你不能进去
Hey, you can't go in!
我是汤姆 摩根  FBI  反恐队
Tom Morgan, FBI. JTTF.
我带着有波图斯111  让我进去
I have a possible POTUS 111. Let me in the building.
好了  孩子们孩子们
Okay, everybody! Everybody!
请大家听我说
Can I have your attention, please?
萨克斯手  记得缩短四分一音符
Saxophones, remember shorter on those quarter notes.
到高潮的时候
And when we get to the crescendo,
"自由的国度"保持住F调
"land of the free," hold that high F.
记得微笑
And smile.
记住了吗  不是每天你们都能为总统演奏的
Okay? It's not every day you get to play for the President!
引爆装置激活
就是这里  还有什么事吗  克劳莉小姐
Here we are. And anything else, Miss Crowley?
没有了  谢谢
No, thanks.
现在欢迎总统内阁
Madam Speaker, the President's Cabinet!
波图斯111  这栋楼里有炸弹
POTUS 111! There's a bomb in the building!
站住  不能进入  没有例外
Stop! No entry! No exceptions!
我是汤姆 摩根  FBI  后退  给我你的手铐
Tom Morgan, FBI. Back up. Give me your cuffs.
-把手铐给我  -别紧张
- Give me your cuffs! - Take it easy!
-把手铐给我  -我给你拿
- Give me your cuffs. - I'm reaching for them.
我给你拿
I'm reaching for them.
先生们女士们
Madam Speaker,
欢迎美国总统
the President of the United States!
关键数据被腐化
Data corruption at critical risk.
你在破坏国家安全计划
You are now in violation of national security protocol.
寻找任何机会
Seeking available options.
上传到卫星系统
Uploading to offsite satellite.
-数据上传中  3%  -鲍曼
- Data upload: 3%. - Bowman?
-她在干嘛  -她在备份她的记忆
- What is she doing? - She's trying to back up her memory
然后传送到别的地方
and send it somewhere else!
-5%.   - 鲍曼
- 5%. - Bowman!
鲍曼
Bowman!
8%
8%.
在过去的三天里  19位美国人
Over the past three days, 19 Americans
在残酷的恐怖行动中失去了生命
have lost their lives to brutal acts of terror...
地道安全员
Tunnel secure.
但是虽然今晚我们的会难过
But I say to you tonight that our hearts may be broken,
但是我们的精神长存
but our spirit will never be broken!
数据上传  17%
Data upload, 17%.
19%
19%.
佩雷  乔伊  你现在是国家的敌人
Perez, Zoe, you are now classified as an enemy of the state.
23%
23%.
25%
25%.
27%  断头台行动启动
27%. Operation Guillotine is in effect.
大约在200年前
It was nearly 200 years ago,
1812年的大战中  弗兰西斯·思考特·基
in the War of 1812, that Francis Scott Key
发现自己被困在去往麦克亨利堡的休战船上
found himself stuck on a truce ship during the shelling of Fort McHenry.
有些人失去了生命
We lost some lives then, too.
但是我们的旗帜一直高高飘扬
But our flag still flew high and proud.
他的所作所为是我们的骄傲
And his admiration became our anthem.
今晚伊利诺斯州海德公园的巴洛学校的
With us tonight is the Youth Orchestra
少年乐队成员将为我们演奏
of the Barrow School from Hyde Park, Illinois.
山姆
Sam.
请大家起立
Let us stand together,
他们让我们的精神振奋  像那面旗帜一样
as they raise our spirits every inch as high as that flag
展示我们永久的团结
to show that our union is still as strong as ever.
啊  你可看见
Oh, say can you see
在晨曦初现时
by the dawn's early light
是什么让我们骄傲地
What so proudly we hailed
在黎明的最后一道曙光中欢呼
at the twilight's last gleaming?
是谁的旗帜在激战中始终高扬
Whose broad stripes and bright stars...
警卫官
Sergeant at Arms?
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
快跑  快跑
Get out, get out.
妈妈
Mom!
杰瑞  太棒了  你做到了
Jerry, all right, you did it!
来  杰瑞
Come on. Yeah, Jerry!
现在还不知道攻击布莱尔地道
There are still no named suspects
和国会大厦嫌疑犯的真实姓名
in the attack on the Blair Tunnel and the attacks in the Capitol Building.
也没有证据表明杰瑞·戴门·肖参与其中
And there is still no word on the involvement of Jerry Damon Shaw.
巨大的刺杀阴谋使
...huge assassination attempt,
运输系统中断
transportation networks disrupted,
没有确认任何嫌疑犯或被拘留
no suspects identified or even arrested...
没有任何线索谁将
any idea who is responsible for what may be
对如此大规模的恐怖炸弹
the largest-scale cyber-terror attack
被安装在美国国内负责
that's ever been mounted in the United States.
众议院和参议院情报委员会
The House and Senate Intelligence Committees
举行秘密会议
meet in closed-door session
讨论如何才能防止这种
to discuss ways to prevent this kind
拆点让阿丽亚项目被取消
of internal security breach that left nearly...
的内部威胁
The Aria project has been decommissioned
所有相关人员被派往别的任务
and all those involved rotated to other assignments.
秘书长先生  我们不能因为这些事
Mr. Secretary, we can’t just stop intelligence-gathering
就停止情报工作
just because of what happened here.
是的  我们不能
No, we can't.
我只知道我们犯了个巨大的错误
All I know is we made a great many mistakes.
许多好人都付出了代价
And good people paid the ultimate price for them.
我们永远也无法偿还他们
And that's a debt we can't ever repay.
但是我们可以给他们荣誉
But we can honor it.
他们的牺牲能时常提醒我们
And we can let their sacrifice remind us that sometimes
我们为我们的自由所做的
the very measures we put into place to safeguard our liberty
成为自由的代价
become threats to liberty itself.
-小朋友  -杰瑞
- Hey, little guy. - Jerry!
瞧你  长大了  你好吗
Look at you, looking older. How are you?
-很好  -生日快乐
- Good. - Happy birthday.
是摇滚乐队耶  送我的吗
It's Rock Band! Is that for me?
不是的  这是给你母亲练习敲鼓的
No, this is so your mom can practice her drumming.
送你的  生日快乐
It is for you. Happy birthday.
山姆  你觉得怎样
Sam, what do you say?
-谢谢  -没关系
- Thanks. - Yeah, no problem.
大家看啊  是摇滚乐队
Guys, look, it's Rock Band!
-太棒了  我们去玩吧  -棒极了
-Cool, let's go. - Awesome!
-对不起  我迟到了  我...  -你能记得真好
- Sorry, I was late. I was... - Thank you for remembering.
是的
Yeah.
很高兴你能来
I'm glad you're here.
我也是
Me, too.